<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP">
    <English>Military Placement (Cust. Obj.)</English>
    <Chinesesimp>军事布局</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMMENT">
    <English>Custom Military Objective</English>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义军事目标</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>启用测试</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables CMP Module Debug</English>
    <Chinesesimp>启用CMP模块调试</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_FACTION">
    <English>Force Faction:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>武力势力</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>Faction of the units to be placed (BLU_F, OPF_F, IND_F, BLU_G_F)</English>
    <Chinesesimp>待放置单元的系数(BLU_F、OPF_F、IND_F、BLU_G_F)</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_PRIORITY">
    <English>Objective priority:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>目标优先级</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_PRIORITY_COMMENT">
    <English>Priority of the custom objective. Used by OPCOM and others for target evaluation</English>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义目标的优先级,用于OPCOM和其他目标评估</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_SIZE">
    <English>Objective size:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>目标大小</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_SIZE_COMMENT">
    <English>Size of the custom objective. Used by OPCOM and others for target evaluation</English>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义目标的大小。用于OPCOM和其他目标评估</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_INFANTRY_COUNT">
    <English>Infantry Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>步兵计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_INFANTRY_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Infantry groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的步兵组计数,如果没有则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MOTORISED_COUNT">
    <English>Motorised Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>摩托化小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MOTORISED_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Motorised groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的摩托化小组的计数,如果没有,则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MECHANISED_COUNT">
    <English>Mechanised Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>机械化小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MECHANISED_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Mechanised groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的机械化小组的计数,如果没有,则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARMOUR_COUNT">
    <English>Armour Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>装甲小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARMOUR_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Armour groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的装甲小组计数,如果没有则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_SPECOPS_COUNT">
    <English>SpecOps Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>特战小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_SPECOPS_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of SpecOps groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的特战小组计数,如果没有则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_HDR_ANTIAIR">
    <English>ANTI-AIR</English>
    <Chinese>防空</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>防空</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>ANTI-AÉREO</Spanish>
    <French>ANTI-AÉRIEN</French>
    <Portuguese>ANTIAÉREO</Portuguese>
    <Russian>ПВО</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_COUNT">
    <English>Spawn AA Units:</English>
    <Chinese>生成防空單位:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>生成防空单位:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Generar unidades AA:</Spanish>
    <French>Apparition unités AA:</French>
    <Portuguese>Gerar unidades AA:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Создать ПВО:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Number of AA (anti-air) units to spawn for this objective. Whole number. 0 = no AA. Scale to TAOR / objective size. Each AA slot routes through the composition spawn validator (envelope 10m, mode "ato") so the unit lands on a clear, non-runway position. Crewed AA engages incoming aircraft via vanilla AI. Class drawn from the AA Classes picker below if non-empty, else from the per-faction default list.</English>
    <Chinese>為此目標生成的防空（AA）單位數量。整數。0 = 不生成防空。依TAOR/目標大小調整。每個防空槽位透過組合生成驗證器（包絡10米，模式 "ato"），確保單位降落在乾淨、非跑道位置。配備人員的防空透過原生AI攻擊來襲飛機。如果下方AA Classes選擇器非空，則從中選擇類別，否則從派系預設清單中選擇。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>为此目标生成的防空（AA）单位数量。整数。0 = 不生成防空。依TAOR/目标大小调整。每个防空槽位通过组合生成验证器（包络10米，模式 "ato"），确保单位降落在干净、非跑道位置。配备人员的防空通过原生AI攻击来袭飞机。如果下方AA Classes选择器非空，则从中选择类别，否则从派系默认列表中选择。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Número de unidades AA (antiaéreas) a generar para este objetivo. Número entero. 0 = sin AA. Ajusta al tamaño del TAOR/objetivo. Cada slot de AA pasa por el validador de generación de composiciones (envoltura 10m, modo "ato") para que la unidad aterrice en una posición despejada, fuera de pista. Las AA tripuladas atacan aeronaves entrantes mediante la IA vanilla. La clase se toma del selector AA Classes inferior si no está vacío, o de la lista por defecto de la facción.</Spanish>
    <French>Nombre d'unités AA (anti-aériennes) à faire apparaître pour cet objectif. Nombre entier. 0 = aucune AA. Adaptez à la taille du TAOR/objectif. Chaque emplacement AA passe par le validateur de position de composition (enveloppe 10m, mode "ato") pour que l'unité atterrisse sur une position dégagée, hors piste. Les AA équipées engagent les aéronefs entrants via l'IA vanilla. La classe est tirée du sélecteur AA Classes ci-dessous s'il n'est pas vide, sinon de la liste par défaut de la faction.</French>
    <Portuguese>Número de unidades AA (antiaéreas) para gerar neste objetivo. Número inteiro. 0 = sem AA. Dimensione ao tamanho do TAOR/objetivo. Cada slot de AA passa pelo validador de geração de composição (envelope 10m, modo "ato") para que a unidade pouse em uma posição limpa, fora da pista. As AA tripuladas engajam aeronaves recebidas via IA vanilla. A classe é tirada do seletor AA Classes abaixo se não estiver vazio, ou da lista padrão por facção.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Количество единиц ПВО (противовоздушных) для создания на этой цели. Целое число. 0 = без ПВО. Масштабируйте по размеру TAOR/цели. Каждый слот ПВО проходит через валидатор позиции композиции (зона 10м, режим "ato"), чтобы юнит появился на чистой позиции вне взлётной полосы. Экипированные ПВО атакуют входящие самолёты через стандартный ИИ. Класс берётся из селектора AA Classes ниже, если он не пуст, иначе из списка по умолчанию для фракции.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR">
    <English>AA Behaviour:</English>
    <Chinese>防空行為:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>防空行为:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Comportamiento AA:</Spanish>
    <French>Comportement AA:</French>
    <Portuguese>Comportamento AA:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Поведение ПВО:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR_COMMENT">
    <English>Static = AA stays at its initial spawn position; OPCOM cannot reposition it. Suitable for fixed defensive emplacements. Roaming = AA participates in OPCOM movement orders alongside other force units; commanders can shift it as the battle develops.</English>
    <Chinese>靜止 = 防空保持在初始生成位置；OPCOM無法重新部署。適用於固定防禦工事。流動 = 防空與其他部隊一同參與OPCOM移動命令；指揮官可隨戰局調整。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>静止 = 防空保持在初始生成位置；OPCOM无法重新部署。适用于固定防御工事。流动 = 防空与其他部队一同参与OPCOM移动命令；指挥官可随战局调整。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Estático = la AA permanece en su posición inicial de aparición; OPCOM no puede reposicionarla. Adecuado para emplazamientos defensivos fijos. Móvil = la AA participa en las órdenes de movimiento de OPCOM junto con otras unidades; los comandantes pueden moverla conforme avanza la batalla.</Spanish>
    <French>Statique = l'AA reste à sa position d'apparition initiale; OPCOM ne peut pas la repositionner. Adapté aux emplacements défensifs fixes. Mobile = l'AA participe aux ordres de mouvement OPCOM aux côtés des autres unités; les commandants peuvent la déplacer au fil de la bataille.</French>
    <Portuguese>Estático = a AA permanece em sua posição inicial de aparecimento; OPCOM não pode reposicioná-la. Adequado para emplacamentos defensivos fixos. Móvel = a AA participa das ordens de movimento OPCOM junto com outras unidades; os comandantes podem movê-la conforme a batalha avança.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Стационарное = ПВО остаётся в начальной позиции появления; OPCOM не может её переместить. Подходит для постоянных оборонительных позиций. Подвижное = ПВО участвует в приказах движения OPCOM наравне с другими боевыми единицами; командиры могут перемещать её по ходу боя.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR_STATIC">
    <English>Static</English>
    <Chinese>靜止</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>静止</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Estático</Spanish>
    <French>Statique</French>
    <Portuguese>Estático</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Стационарное</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR_ROAMING">
    <English>Roaming</English>
    <Chinese>流動</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>流动</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Móvil</Spanish>
    <French>Mobile</French>
    <Portuguese>Móvel</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Подвижное</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_CLASSES">
    <English>AA Classes:</English>
    <Chinese>防空分類:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>防空分类:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Clases AA:</Spanish>
    <French>Classes AA:</French>
    <Portuguese>Classes AA:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Классы ПВО:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_CLASSES_COMMENT">
    <English>Multi-select listbox of AA-shape vehicle classes for this faction. Filter cycle: All / Vehicle / Static (StaticWeapon descendants). Default selection is empty - leave empty to use the per-faction fallback list (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). The Override Entries field accepts comma-separated mod classnames the listbox doesn't surface. Multi-select: left-click selects one row; Ctrl+left-click toggles individual rows; Shift+left-click selects a range.</English>
    <Chinese>適用於此派系的防空形態載具類別多選清單。篩選循環: 全部 / 載具 / 靜止（StaticWeapon子類）。預設選擇為空 - 留空以使用每派系後備清單（ALIVE_factionDefaultAA）。Override Entries 欄位接受逗號分隔的、清單未列出的模組類別名稱。多選: 左鍵點擊選擇一行；Ctrl+左鍵切換單行；Shift+左鍵選擇範圍。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>适用于此派系的防空形态载具类别多选列表。筛选循环: 全部 / 载具 / 静止（StaticWeapon子类）。默认选择为空 - 留空以使用每派系备用列表（ALIVE_factionDefaultAA）。Override Entries 字段接受逗号分隔的、列表未呈现的模组类名。多选: 左键点击选择一行；Ctrl+左键切换单行；Shift+左键选择范围。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Listbox multiselección de clases de vehículos con forma AA para esta facción. Ciclo de filtro: Todo / Vehículo / Estático (descendientes de StaticWeapon). La selección por defecto está vacía - déjala vacía para usar la lista de respaldo por facción (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). El campo Override Entries acepta classnames de mods separados por comas que el listbox no muestra. Multiselección: clic-izquierdo selecciona una fila; Ctrl+clic-izquierdo alterna filas individuales; Shift+clic-izquierdo selecciona un rango.</Spanish>
    <French>Listbox multi-sélection des classes de véhicules de forme AA pour cette faction. Cycle de filtre: Tout / Véhicule / Statique (descendants de StaticWeapon). La sélection par défaut est vide - laissez vide pour utiliser la liste de repli par faction (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). Le champ Override Entries accepte des classnames de mods séparés par des virgules que la listbox n'affiche pas. Multi-sélection: clic-gauche sélectionne une ligne; Ctrl+clic-gauche bascule les lignes individuelles; Shift+clic-gauche sélectionne une plage.</French>
    <Portuguese>Listbox de seleção múltipla de classes de veículos em forma de AA para esta facção. Ciclo de filtro: Todos / Veículo / Estático (descendentes de StaticWeapon). A seleção padrão está vazia - deixe vazia para usar a lista de fallback por facção (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). O campo Override Entries aceita classnames de mods separados por vírgulas que a listbox não mostra. Seleção múltipla: clique-esquerdo seleciona uma linha; Ctrl+clique-esquerdo alterna linhas individuais; Shift+clique-esquerdo seleciona um intervalo.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Список с множественным выбором классов техники формы ПВО для этой фракции. Цикл фильтра: Все / Транспорт / Стационарные (потомки StaticWeapon). Выбор по умолчанию пуст - оставьте пустым для использования резервного списка по фракции (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). Поле Override Entries принимает имена классов модов через запятую, которые список не отображает. Множественный выбор: левый клик выбирает одну строку; Ctrl+левый клик переключает отдельные строки; Shift+левый клик выбирает диапазон.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION">
    <English>Spawn Composition:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>平民放置</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_COMMENT">
    <English>Multi-select listbox of compositions valid for the module's faction (Military for WEST/EAST, Guerrilla for RESISTANCE). At spawn time the validator tries the ticked compositions in shuffled order at three search tiers (50m / 150m / 300m) and uses the first that fits the surrounding terrain, so a tight site can still get a spawn from an alternative pick in the pool. The Override field accepts free-text class names for mod compositions the listbox doesn't surface. Empty selection = no composition spawn. Multi-select: Ctrl+click toggles individual rows, Shift+click selects a range, plain click replaces with just that one row.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>输入组合的类型(总部,要塞,直升机机场等)或者组合类名</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_A">
    <English>BIS - Camp Audacity</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Audacity营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_B">
    <English>BIS - Camp Bravery</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Bravery营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_C">
    <English>BIS - Camp Courage</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Courage营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_D">
    <English>BIS - Camp Defiance</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Defiance营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_E">
    <English>BIS - Camp Endurance</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Endurance营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_F">
    <English>BIS - Camp Fortitude</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Fortitude营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_HQ">
    <English>Create as HQ:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>创建为总部</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_HQ_COMMENT">
    <English>Selects HQ objective close to the module or if unavailable spawns an HQ composition at the module position</English>
    <Chinesesimp>选择模块附近的总部目标,或者如果不可用,则在模块位置生成总部合成</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_FIELD_HQ">
    <English>Auto Field HQ if empty:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_FIELD_HQ_COMMENT">
    <English>Auto-fill fallback for the Spawn Composition picker. When the picker is empty and this is set to Yes, a random FieldHQ-class composition spawns near the module (validator-checked, 3-tier 50m / 200m / 500m search). When the picker has any tick or override class, this toggle is ignored and the picked composition takes precedence. Use when the spot needs an HQ but the specific composition doesn't matter.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_USAGE">
    <English>Place the Custom Military Objective module in the editor, select the desired Size, Priority and force composition. Custom factions can be entered in the text box (separated by a comma).</English>
    <Chinesesimp>将“自定义军事目标”模块放入编辑器中,选择所需的大小、优先级和部队组成。可以在文本框中输入自定义派别(用逗号分隔)。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_READINESS_LEVEL">
    <English>Readiness:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>准备就绪:</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_READINESS_LEVEL_COMMENT">
    <English>The amount of troops that will be on duty and patrolling</English>
    <Chinesesimp>即将执勤和巡逻的部队数量</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_ALLOW_PLAYER_TASK">
    <English>Allow player tasking:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>允许玩家任务:</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_ALLOW_PLAYER_TASK_COMMENT">
    <English>MilAssault/MilDefend C2ISTAR tasks</English>
    <Chinesesimp>C2ISTAR军事进攻/军事防御任务</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
