<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP">
    <English>Military Placement (Cust. Obj.)</English>
    <Chinesesimp>军事布局</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMMENT">
    <English>Custom Military Objective</English>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义军事目标</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>启用测试</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables CMP Module Debug</English>
    <Chinesesimp>启用CMP模块调试</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_FACTION">
    <English>Force Faction:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>武力势力</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>Faction of the units to be placed (BLU_F, OPF_F, IND_F, BLU_G_F)</English>
    <Chinesesimp>待放置单元的系数(BLU_F、OPF_F、IND_F、BLU_G_F)</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_PRIORITY">
    <English>Objective priority:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>目标优先级</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_PRIORITY_COMMENT">
    <English>Priority of the custom objective. Used by OPCOM and others for target evaluation</English>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义目标的优先级,用于OPCOM和其他目标评估</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_SIZE">
    <English>Objective size:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>目标大小</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_SIZE_COMMENT">
    <English>Radius (in metres) of the custom objective. Defines the area within which the picked composition, AA pods, supplies, and objective scenery objects are placed. Also used by OPCOM and intel for target evaluation.</English>
    <Chinese>自訂目標的半徑（以公尺為單位）。定義了已選擇的組合、防空陣地、補給品和目標場景物件的放置區域。同時用於OPCOM和情報的目標評估。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义目标的半径（以公尺为单位）。定义了已选择的组合、防空阵地、补给品和目标场景物件的放置区域。同时用于OPCOM和情报的目标评估。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Radio (en metros) del objetivo personalizado. Define el área dentro de la cual se colocan la composición seleccionada, los emplazamientos AA, los suministros y los objetos decorativos del objetivo. También usado por OPCOM e inteligencia para la evaluación de objetivos.</Spanish>
    <French>Rayon (en mètres) de l'objectif personnalisé. Définit la zone dans laquelle sont placés la composition sélectionnée, les pièces AA, les ravitaillements et les objets décoratifs de l'objectif. Également utilisé par OPCOM et le renseignement pour l'évaluation des objectifs.</French>
    <Portuguese>Raio (em metros) do objetivo personalizado. Define a área dentro da qual são colocados a composição selecionada, as posições AA, os suprimentos e os objetos decorativos do objetivo. Também usado pelo OPCOM e inteligência para avaliação de objetivos.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Радиус (в метрах) пользовательской цели. Определяет область, внутри которой размещаются выбранная композиция, ПВО, припасы и декоративные объекты цели. Также используется OPCOM и разведкой для оценки целей.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_INFANTRY_COUNT">
    <English>Infantry Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>步兵计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_INFANTRY_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Infantry groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的步兵组计数,如果没有则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MOTORISED_COUNT">
    <English>Motorised Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>摩托化小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MOTORISED_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Motorised groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的摩托化小组的计数,如果没有,则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MECHANISED_COUNT">
    <English>Mechanised Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>机械化小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_MECHANISED_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Mechanised groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的机械化小组的计数,如果没有,则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARMOUR_COUNT">
    <English>Armour Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>装甲小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARMOUR_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of Armour groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的装甲小组计数,如果没有则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARTILLERY_COUNT">
    <English>Artillery Count:</English>
    <Chinese>砲兵數量:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>炮兵数量:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Número de piezas de artillería:</Spanish>
    <French>Nombre de pièces d'artillerie:</French>
    <Portuguese>Contagem de Artilharia:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Количество артиллерии:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARTILLERY_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of artillery sections to be spawned, set to 0 for none. Drawn from the faction's artillery groups; factions without artillery groups get batteries composed directly from their artillery vehicles instead (self-propelled guns preferred).</English>
    <Chinese>設定要生成的砲兵分隊數量，設為0則不生成。取自該派系的砲兵小隊；若派系沒有砲兵小隊，則改由該派系的砲兵載具直接編成砲兵連(優先採用自走砲)。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>设置生成的炮兵分队数量,设为0则不生成。取自该阵营编制内的炮兵小队;若阵营没有炮兵小队,则改由其炮兵车辆直接组成炮兵连(优先选用自行火炮)。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Establece el número de secciones de artillería que se generarán; establezca 0 para ninguna. Se toman de los grupos de artillería de la facción; las facciones sin grupos de artillería reciben en su lugar baterías compuestas directamente a partir de sus vehículos de artillería (se prefieren las piezas autopropulsadas).</Spanish>
    <French>Définit le nombre de sections d'artillerie à faire apparaître, mettre à 0 pour aucune. Tirées des groupes d'artillerie de la faction; les factions dépourvues de groupes d'artillerie reçoivent à la place des batteries composées directement à partir de leurs véhicules d'artillerie (canons automoteurs privilégiés).</French>
    <Portuguese>Define a quantidade de seções de artilharia a serem geradas; defina 0 para nenhuma. Extraídas dos grupos de artilharia da facção; facções sem grupos de artilharia recebem baterias compostas diretamente a partir de seus veículos de artilharia (canhões autopropulsados preferidos).</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Задайте количество создаваемых артиллерийских подразделений, 0 - без артиллерии. Выбираются из артиллерийских групп фракции; для фракций без артиллерийских групп батареи формируются непосредственно из их артиллерийских машин (предпочтение отдаётся самоходным орудиям).</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARTILLERY_FACTION">
    <English>Artillery Faction:</English>
    <Chinese>砲兵派系:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>炮兵阵营:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Facción de artillería:</Spanish>
    <French>Faction d'artillerie:</French>
    <Portuguese>Facção de Artilharia:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Фракция артиллерии:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARTILLERY_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>Optional. Draw the placed artillery from this donor faction instead of the composition factions - models batteries attached from a sister branch, for example RHS Tank Troops guns supporting Motor Rifles. Only factions that field artillery are listed; the donor must fight for the same side. Uses the donor's artillery groups when it defines them, otherwise composes batteries from its artillery vehicles. Select (none) to use the composition factions.</English>
    <Chinese>可選。改由此支援派系提供放置的砲兵，而非編組派系——模擬由友軍分支支援的砲兵連，例如以RHS戰車部隊的火砲支援機械化步兵。僅列出擁有砲兵的派系，且支援派系須與同一陣營作戰。若支援派系有定義砲兵小隊則優先採用，否則改由其砲兵載具編成砲兵連。選擇「(無)」則使用編組派系。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>可选。改从此供体阵营抽取部署的炮兵,而非使用编组阵营——用于模拟由友邻兵种附属支援的炮兵连,例如RHS坦克部队的火炮支援摩托化步兵。仅列出拥有炮兵编制的阵营,且供体阵营须与本方同一阵营作战。若供体阵营定义了炮兵小队则优先使用,否则由其炮兵车辆组成炮兵连。选择“(无)”则使用编组阵营。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Opcional. Obtiene la artillería colocada de esta facción donante en lugar de las facciones de la composición; representa baterías adscritas de una rama hermana, por ejemplo piezas de los Cuerpos de Tanques RHS apoyando a Infantería Motorizada. Solo se listan las facciones que disponen de artillería; la donante debe combatir por el mismo bando. Usa los grupos de artillería de la donante cuando los define, o en su defecto compone baterías a partir de sus vehículos de artillería. Seleccione (ninguna) para usar las facciones de la composición.</Spanish>
    <French>Facultatif. Tire l'artillerie déployée de cette faction donneuse plutôt que des factions de la composition - modélise des batteries rattachées d'une branche sœur, par exemple des pièces des troupes blindées RHS appuyant l'infanterie motorisée. Seules les factions disposant d'artillerie sont listées; la faction donneuse doit combattre dans le même camp. Utilise les groupes d'artillerie de la faction donneuse lorsqu'elle en définit, sinon compose les batteries à partir de ses véhicules d'artillerie. Sélectionnez (aucune) pour utiliser les factions de la composition.</French>
    <Portuguese>Opcional. Extrai a artilharia posicionada desta facção doadora em vez das facções da composição - representa baterias vinculadas de um ramo irmão, por exemplo canhões das Tropas de Tanques da RHS apoiando os Fuzileiros Motorizados. Somente facções que possuem artilharia são listadas; a doadora deve lutar pelo mesmo lado. Usa os grupos de artilharia da doadora quando definidos, ou compõe baterias a partir de seus veículos de artilharia. Selecione (nenhuma) para usar as facções da composição.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Необязательно. Формировать размещаемую артиллерию из этой фракции-донора вместо фракций состава - моделирует батареи, приданные из смежного рода войск, например орудия RHS танковых войск, поддерживающие мотострелков. Перечислены только фракции, располагающие артиллерией; донор должен воевать на той же стороне. Использует артиллерийские группы донора, если они определены, иначе формирует батареи из его артиллерийских машин. Выберите (нет), чтобы использовать фракции состава.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARTILLERY_SECTION_SIZE">
    <English>Artillery Section Size (guns):</English>
    <Chinese>砲兵編組規模（火砲數）:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>炮兵编组规模（火炮数）:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Tamaño de la sección de artillería (piezas):</Spanish>
    <French>Taille de la section d'artillerie (pièces):</French>
    <Portuguese>Tamanho da seção de artilharia (peças):</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Размер артиллерийской секции (орудий):</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_ARTILLERY_SECTION_SIZE_COMMENT">
    <English>Number of guns per battery when artillery is composed from vehicles (factions whose guns have no dedicated artillery group, for example RHS M252/M119). A realistic mortar section or howitzer battery is 4 guns. Larger sections place more guns and crews. Factions that field their own artillery groups keep the group's own size.</English>
    <Chinese>當砲兵以載具編成時（其火砲未定義專屬砲兵小隊的派系，例如RHS的M252/M119），每個砲兵連的火砲數量。真實的迫擊砲排或榴彈砲連為4門。編組越大，放置的火砲與乘員也越多。擁有自身砲兵小隊的派系仍沿用該小隊的既有規模。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>当炮兵由车辆组成时（其火炮未定义专属炮兵小队的阵营，例如RHS的M252/M119），每个炮兵连的火炮数量。真实的迫击炮排或榴弹炮连为4门。编组越大，放置的火炮与乘员也越多。拥有自身炮兵小队的阵营仍沿用该小队的既有规模。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Número de piezas por batería cuando la artillería se compone a partir de vehículos (facciones cuyas piezas no tienen un grupo de artillería propio, por ejemplo el M252/M119 de RHS). Una sección de morteros o batería de obuses realista tiene 4 piezas. Las secciones más grandes colocan más piezas y dotaciones. Las facciones que disponen de sus propios grupos de artillería conservan el tamaño del grupo.</Spanish>
    <French>Nombre de pièces par batterie lorsque l'artillerie est composée à partir de véhicules (factions dont les pièces n'ont pas de groupe d'artillerie dédié, par exemple les M252/M119 de RHS). Une section de mortiers ou une batterie d'obusiers réaliste compte 4 pièces. Les sections plus grandes déploient plus de pièces et leurs équipages. Les factions disposant de leurs propres groupes d'artillerie conservent la taille du groupe.</French>
    <Portuguese>Número de peças por bateria quando a artilharia é composta a partir de veículos (facções cujas peças não têm um grupo de artilharia próprio, por exemplo o M252/M119 da RHS). Uma seção de morteiros ou bateria de obuses realista tem 4 peças. Seções maiores posicionam mais peças e guarnições. Facções que possuem seus próprios grupos de artilharia mantêm o tamanho do grupo.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Количество орудий в батарее, когда артиллерия формируется из машин (фракции, чьи орудия не имеют выделенной артиллерийской группы, например M252/M119 из RHS). Реалистичный миномётный взвод или гаубичная батарея — 4 орудия. Более крупные секции размещают больше орудий и расчётов. Фракции с собственными артиллерийскими группами сохраняют размер группы.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_GARRISON_COMPOSITIONS">
    <English>Garrison compositions:</English>
    <Chinese>駐守組合設施:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>驻守组合设施:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Guarnecer composiciones:</Spanish>
    <French>Occuper les compositions:</French>
    <Portuguese>Guarnecer composições:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Гарнизоны в композициях:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_GARRISON_COMPOSITIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>Divert part of this objective's guard force to man spawned camps, Field HQs and objective compositions. Guards hold their posts and are not re-tasked by the AI commander. The diverted share is sized to the composition's defensible positions; the total guard count is unchanged.</English>
    <Chinese>將此目標的部分守衛兵力調派至生成的營地、野戰指揮部及目標組合設施駐守。守衛會堅守崗位，不會被AI指揮官重新指派任務。調派比例依組合設施的可防禦位置數量而定；守衛總數維持不變。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>将此目标的部分守卫兵力调派至生成的营地、野战指挥部及目标组合设施驻守。守卫会坚守岗位,不会被AI指挥官重新指派任务。调派比例依组合设施的可防御位置数量而定;守卫总数保持不变。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Desvía parte de la fuerza de guardia de este objetivo para dotar los campamentos, puestos de mando de campaña y composiciones del objetivo generados. Los guardias mantienen sus puestos y el comandante de IA no les reasigna tareas. La proporción desviada se ajusta a las posiciones defendibles de la composición; el total de guardias no cambia.</Spanish>
    <French>Détourne une partie de la force de garde de cet objectif pour occuper les camps, PC de campagne et compositions d'objectif générés. Les gardes tiennent leurs postes et ne sont pas réaffectés par le commandant IA. La part détournée est dimensionnée selon les positions défendables de la composition; le total de gardes reste inchangé.</French>
    <Portuguese>Desvia parte da força de guarda deste objetivo para ocupar os acampamentos, QGs de campanha e composições de objetivo gerados. Os guardas mantêm seus postos e não são redirecionados pelo comandante de IA. A parcela desviada é dimensionada pelas posições defensáveis da composição; o total de guardas permanece inalterado.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Направляет часть охранных сил этой цели в созданные лагеря, полевые штабы и композиции цели. Гарнизоны удерживают свои посты и не переназначаются ИИ-командующим. Доля рассчитывается по числу оборонительных позиций композиции; общее число охраны не меняется.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_SPECOPS_COUNT">
    <English>SpecOps Count:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>特战小组计数</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CUSTOM_SPECOPS_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Set count of SpecOps groups to be spawned, set to 0 for none</English>
    <Chinesesimp>设置要生成的特战小组计数,如果没有则设置为0</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_HDR_ANTIAIR">
    <English>ANTI-AIR</English>
    <Chinese>防空</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>防空</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>ANTI-AÉREO</Spanish>
    <French>ANTI-AÉRIEN</French>
    <Portuguese>ANTIAÉREO</Portuguese>
    <Russian>ПВО</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_COUNT">
    <English>Spawn AA Units:</English>
    <Chinese>生成防空單位:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>生成防空单位:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Generar unidades AA:</Spanish>
    <French>Apparition unités AA:</French>
    <Portuguese>Gerar unidades AA:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Создать ПВО:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_COUNT_COMMENT">
    <English>Number of AA (anti-air) units to spawn for this objective. Whole number. 0 = no AA. Scale to TAOR / objective size. Each AA slot routes through the composition spawn validator (envelope 10m, mode "ato") so the unit lands on a clear, non-runway position. Crewed AA engages incoming aircraft via vanilla AI. Class drawn from the AA Classes picker below if non-empty, else from the per-faction default list.</English>
    <Chinese>為此目標生成的防空（AA）單位數量。整數。0 = 不生成防空。依TAOR/目標大小調整。每個防空槽位透過組合生成驗證器（包絡10米，模式 "ato"），確保單位降落在乾淨、非跑道位置。配備人員的防空透過原生AI攻擊來襲飛機。如果下方AA Classes選擇器非空，則從中選擇類別，否則從派系預設清單中選擇。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>为此目标生成的防空（AA）单位数量。整数。0 = 不生成防空。依TAOR/目标大小调整。每个防空槽位通过组合生成验证器（包络10米，模式 "ato"），确保单位降落在干净、非跑道位置。配备人员的防空通过原生AI攻击来袭飞机。如果下方AA Classes选择器非空，则从中选择类别，否则从派系默认列表中选择。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Número de unidades AA (antiaéreas) a generar para este objetivo. Número entero. 0 = sin AA. Ajusta al tamaño del TAOR/objetivo. Cada slot de AA pasa por el validador de generación de composiciones (envoltura 10m, modo "ato") para que la unidad aterrice en una posición despejada, fuera de pista. Las AA tripuladas atacan aeronaves entrantes mediante la IA vanilla. La clase se toma del selector AA Classes inferior si no está vacío, o de la lista por defecto de la facción.</Spanish>
    <French>Nombre d'unités AA (anti-aériennes) à faire apparaître pour cet objectif. Nombre entier. 0 = aucune AA. Adaptez à la taille du TAOR/objectif. Chaque emplacement AA passe par le validateur de position de composition (enveloppe 10m, mode "ato") pour que l'unité atterrisse sur une position dégagée, hors piste. Les AA équipées engagent les aéronefs entrants via l'IA vanilla. La classe est tirée du sélecteur AA Classes ci-dessous s'il n'est pas vide, sinon de la liste par défaut de la faction.</French>
    <Portuguese>Número de unidades AA (antiaéreas) para gerar neste objetivo. Número inteiro. 0 = sem AA. Dimensione ao tamanho do TAOR/objetivo. Cada slot de AA passa pelo validador de geração de composição (envelope 10m, modo "ato") para que a unidade pouse em uma posição limpa, fora da pista. As AA tripuladas engajam aeronaves recebidas via IA vanilla. A classe é tirada do seletor AA Classes abaixo se não estiver vazio, ou da lista padrão por facção.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Количество единиц ПВО (противовоздушных) для создания на этой цели. Целое число. 0 = без ПВО. Масштабируйте по размеру TAOR/цели. Каждый слот ПВО проходит через валидатор позиции композиции (зона 10м, режим "ato"), чтобы юнит появился на чистой позиции вне взлётной полосы. Экипированные ПВО атакуют входящие самолёты через стандартный ИИ. Класс берётся из селектора AA Classes ниже, если он не пуст, иначе из списка по умолчанию для фракции.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR">
    <English>AA Behaviour:</English>
    <Chinese>防空行為:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>防空行为:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Comportamiento AA:</Spanish>
    <French>Comportement AA:</French>
    <Portuguese>Comportamento AA:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Поведение ПВО:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR_COMMENT">
    <English>Static = AA stays at its initial spawn position; OPCOM cannot reposition it. Suitable for fixed defensive emplacements. Roaming = AA participates in OPCOM movement orders alongside other force units; commanders can shift it as the battle develops.</English>
    <Chinese>靜止 = 防空保持在初始生成位置；OPCOM無法重新部署。適用於固定防禦工事。流動 = 防空與其他部隊一同參與OPCOM移動命令；指揮官可隨戰局調整。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>静止 = 防空保持在初始生成位置；OPCOM无法重新部署。适用于固定防御工事。流动 = 防空与其他部队一同参与OPCOM移动命令；指挥官可随战局调整。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Estático = la AA permanece en su posición inicial de aparición; OPCOM no puede reposicionarla. Adecuado para emplazamientos defensivos fijos. Móvil = la AA participa en las órdenes de movimiento de OPCOM junto con otras unidades; los comandantes pueden moverla conforme avanza la batalla.</Spanish>
    <French>Statique = l'AA reste à sa position d'apparition initiale; OPCOM ne peut pas la repositionner. Adapté aux emplacements défensifs fixes. Mobile = l'AA participe aux ordres de mouvement OPCOM aux côtés des autres unités; les commandants peuvent la déplacer au fil de la bataille.</French>
    <Portuguese>Estático = a AA permanece em sua posição inicial de aparecimento; OPCOM não pode reposicioná-la. Adequado para emplacamentos defensivos fixos. Móvel = a AA participa das ordens de movimento OPCOM junto com outras unidades; os comandantes podem movê-la conforme a batalha avança.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Стационарное = ПВО остаётся в начальной позиции появления; OPCOM не может её переместить. Подходит для постоянных оборонительных позиций. Подвижное = ПВО участвует в приказах движения OPCOM наравне с другими боевыми единицами; командиры могут перемещать её по ходу боя.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR_STATIC">
    <English>Static</English>
    <Chinese>靜止</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>静止</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Estático</Spanish>
    <French>Statique</French>
    <Portuguese>Estático</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Стационарное</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_BEHAVIOUR_ROAMING">
    <English>Roaming</English>
    <Chinese>流動</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>流动</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Móvil</Spanish>
    <French>Mobile</French>
    <Portuguese>Móvel</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Подвижное</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_CLASSES">
    <English>AA Classes:</English>
    <Chinese>防空分類:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>防空分类:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Clases AA:</Spanish>
    <French>Classes AA:</French>
    <Portuguese>Classes AA:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Классы ПВО:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_AA_CLASSES_COMMENT">
    <English>Multi-select listbox of AA-shape vehicle classes for this faction. Filter cycle: All / Vehicle / Static (StaticWeapon descendants). Default selection is empty - leave empty to use the per-faction fallback list (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). The Override Entries field accepts comma-separated mod classnames the listbox doesn't surface. Multi-select: left-click selects one row; Ctrl+left-click toggles individual rows; Shift+left-click selects a range. NOTE: this is a per-module override - any selection here always wins over ALIVE_factionDefaultAA. Mission staticData.sqf hashSet calls on ALIVE_factionDefaultAA only affect runtime when this picker is empty.</English>
    <Chinese>適用於此派系的防空形態載具類別多選清單。篩選循環: 全部 / 載具 / 靜止（StaticWeapon子類）。預設選擇為空 - 留空以使用每派系後備清單（ALIVE_factionDefaultAA）。Override Entries 欄位接受逗號分隔的、清單未列出的模組類別名稱。多選: 左鍵點擊選擇一行；Ctrl+左鍵切換單行；Shift+左鍵選擇範圍。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>适用于此派系的防空形态载具类别多选列表。筛选循环: 全部 / 载具 / 静止（StaticWeapon子类）。默认选择为空 - 留空以使用每派系备用列表（ALIVE_factionDefaultAA）。Override Entries 字段接受逗号分隔的、列表未呈现的模组类名。多选: 左键点击选择一行；Ctrl+左键切换单行；Shift+左键选择范围。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Listbox multiselección de clases de vehículos con forma AA para esta facción. Ciclo de filtro: Todo / Vehículo / Estático (descendientes de StaticWeapon). La selección por defecto está vacía - déjala vacía para usar la lista de respaldo por facción (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). El campo Override Entries acepta classnames de mods separados por comas que el listbox no muestra. Multiselección: clic-izquierdo selecciona una fila; Ctrl+clic-izquierdo alterna filas individuales; Shift+clic-izquierdo selecciona un rango.</Spanish>
    <French>Listbox multi-sélection des classes de véhicules de forme AA pour cette faction. Cycle de filtre: Tout / Véhicule / Statique (descendants de StaticWeapon). La sélection par défaut est vide - laissez vide pour utiliser la liste de repli par faction (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). Le champ Override Entries accepte des classnames de mods séparés par des virgules que la listbox n'affiche pas. Multi-sélection: clic-gauche sélectionne une ligne; Ctrl+clic-gauche bascule les lignes individuelles; Shift+clic-gauche sélectionne une plage.</French>
    <Portuguese>Listbox de seleção múltipla de classes de veículos em forma de AA para esta facção. Ciclo de filtro: Todos / Veículo / Estático (descendentes de StaticWeapon). A seleção padrão está vazia - deixe vazia para usar a lista de fallback por facção (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). O campo Override Entries aceita classnames de mods separados por vírgulas que a listbox não mostra. Seleção múltipla: clique-esquerdo seleciona uma linha; Ctrl+clique-esquerdo alterna linhas individuais; Shift+clique-esquerdo seleciona um intervalo.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Список с множественным выбором классов техники формы ПВО для этой фракции. Цикл фильтра: Все / Транспорт / Стационарные (потомки StaticWeapon). Выбор по умолчанию пуст - оставьте пустым для использования резервного списка по фракции (ALIVE_factionDefaultAA). Поле Override Entries принимает имена классов модов через запятую, которые список не отображает. Множественный выбор: левый клик выбирает одну строку; Ctrl+левый клик переключает отдельные строки; Shift+левый клик выбирает диапазон.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION">
    <English>Spawn Composition:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>平民放置</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_COMMENT">
    <English>Multi-select listbox of compositions valid for the module's faction (Military for WEST/EAST, Guerrilla for RESISTANCE). At spawn time the validator tries the ticked compositions in shuffled order at three search tiers (50m / 150m / 300m) and uses the first that fits the surrounding terrain, so a tight site can still get a spawn from an alternative pick in the pool. The Override field accepts free-text class names for mod compositions the listbox doesn't surface. Empty selection = no composition spawn. Multi-select: Ctrl+click toggles individual rows, Shift+click selects a range, plain click replaces with just that one row.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>输入组合的类型(总部,要塞,直升机机场等)或者组合类名</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_A">
    <English>BIS - Camp Audacity</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Audacity营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_B">
    <English>BIS - Camp Bravery</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Bravery营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_C">
    <English>BIS - Camp Courage</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Courage营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_D">
    <English>BIS - Camp Defiance</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Defiance营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_E">
    <English>BIS - Camp Endurance</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Endurance营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_COMPOSITION_BIS_F">
    <English>BIS - Camp Fortitude</English>
    <Chinesesimp>BIS-Fortitude营地</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_HQ">
    <English>Create as HQ:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>创建为总部</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_HQ_COMMENT">
    <English>Selects HQ objective close to the module or if unavailable spawns an HQ composition at the module position</English>
    <Chinesesimp>选择模块附近的总部目标,或者如果不可用,则在模块位置生成总部合成</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_FIELD_HQ">
    <English>Auto Field HQ if empty:</English>
    <Chinese>若為空則自動生成野戰指揮部:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>为空时自动生成野战指挥部:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Auto Puesto de Mando de Campaña si está vacío:</Spanish>
    <French>PC de campagne auto si vide:</French>
    <Portuguese>Auto QG de Campanha se vazio:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Авто-полевой ШТАБ, если пусто:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_CREATE_FIELD_HQ_COMMENT">
    <English>Auto-fill fallback for the Spawn Composition picker. When the picker is empty and this is set to Yes, a random FieldHQ-class composition spawns near the module (validator-checked, 3-tier 50m / 200m / 500m search). When the picker has any tick or override class, this toggle is ignored and the picked composition takes precedence. Use when the spot needs an HQ but the specific composition doesn't matter.</English>
    <Chinese>生成組合選取器為空時的自動填入備援。當選取器為空且此項設為「是」時，會在模組附近生成隨機的 FieldHQ 類編組（經驗證器檢查，採 3 層 50 公尺 / 200 公尺 / 500 公尺搜尋）。若選取器中有任何勾選項目或覆寫類別，此開關會被忽略，改以所選編組優先。適用於該地點需要指揮部但具體編組不重要的情況。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>生成组合选择器为空时的自动填充后备方案。当选择器为空且此项设为“是”时,会在模块附近生成一个随机的野战指挥部(FieldHQ)类组合(经过验证器检查,采用 50 米 / 200 米 / 500 米三级搜索)。当选择器中有任意勾选项或覆盖类别时,此开关将被忽略,已选组合优先生效。适用于需要指挥部但具体组合不重要的场合。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Relleno automático de reserva para el selector de Composición de Aparición. Cuando el selector está vacío y esto está en Sí, aparece una composición aleatoria de clase FieldHQ cerca del módulo (validada, búsqueda de 3 niveles 50m / 200m / 500m). Cuando el selector tiene alguna marca o clase de anulación, este ajuste se ignora y la composición elegida tiene prioridad. Usar cuando el lugar necesita un puesto de mando pero la composición específica no importa.</Spanish>
    <French>Solution de repli automatique pour le sélecteur de composition à faire apparaître. Quand le sélecteur est vide et que ce réglage est sur Oui, une composition aléatoire de classe PC de campagne apparaît près du module (validée, recherche en 3 paliers 50 m / 200 m / 500 m). Quand le sélecteur contient une coche ou une classe de remplacement, ce réglage est ignoré et la composition choisie a priorité. À utiliser quand l'emplacement nécessite un PC mais que la composition précise importe peu.</French>
    <Portuguese>Preenchimento automático de contingência para o seletor de Composição de Surgimento. Quando o seletor está vazio e esta opção está definida como Sim, uma composição aleatória da classe FieldHQ surge perto do módulo (verificado por validador, busca em 3 níveis de 50m / 200m / 500m). Quando o seletor tem qualquer marcação ou classe substituta, esta opção é ignorada e a composição escolhida tem prioridade. Use quando o local precisa de um QG, mas a composição específica não importa.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Резервное автозаполнение для выбора состава размещения. Если выбор пуст и этот параметр установлен в "Да", рядом с модулем создаётся случайный состав класса FieldHQ (проверяется валидатором, трёхуровневый поиск 50 м / 200 м / 500 м). Если в выборе есть отметка или переопределение класса, этот переключатель игнорируется, и выбранный состав имеет приоритет. Используйте, когда точке нужен штаб, но конкретный состав не важен.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_USAGE">
    <English>Place the Custom Military Objective module in the editor, select the desired Size, Priority and force composition. Custom factions can be entered in the text box (separated by a comma).</English>
    <Chinesesimp>将“自定义军事目标”模块放入编辑器中,选择所需的大小、优先级和部队组成。可以在文本框中输入自定义派别(用逗号分隔)。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_READINESS_LEVEL">
    <English>Readiness:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>准备就绪:</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_READINESS_LEVEL_COMMENT">
    <English>The amount of troops that will be on duty and patrolling</English>
    <Chinesesimp>即将执勤和巡逻的部队数量</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_ALLOW_PLAYER_TASK">
    <English>Allow player tasking:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>允许玩家任务:</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CMP_ALLOW_PLAYER_TASK_COMMENT">
    <English>MilAssault/MilDefend C2ISTAR tasks</English>
    <Chinesesimp>C2ISTAR军事进攻/军事防御任务</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
