<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_COMBATSUPPORT">
    <English>Player Combat Support</English>
    <Chinesesimp>玩家战斗支持</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_COMMENT">
    <English>ALiVE Combat Support System (CAS/Artillery/Transport)</English>
    <Chinesesimp>现役作战支持系统（空对地/火炮/运输）</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_ALLOW">
    <English>Access Item Categories:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_CUSTOM_ITEMS">
    <English>Custom Access Items (classnames):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_CUSTOM_ITEMS_COMMENT">
    <English>Comma-separated list of additional item classnames that should grant Combat Support access on top of the Access Item Categories above. Use this for mod-supplied items that don't fit a registered category (e.g. a custom faction's command tablet, a campaign-specific radio). Classnames are matched literally and case-insensitively against the player's assigned items / uniform / vest / backpack. Example: "MyMod_CommandTablet, AnotherMod_FieldRadio". Leave empty for none.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CAS_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Total number of times destroyed CAS aircraft can be replaced, shared across all CAS assets. 0 disables replacement.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CAS_LIMIT">
    <English>CAS Respawn Limit:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>空中支援限额</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_TRANS_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Total number of times destroyed transport aircraft can be replaced, shared across all transport assets. 0 disables replacement.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ARTY_LIMIT">
    <English>Artillery Respawn Limit:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ARTY_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Total number of times destroyed artillery batteries can be replaced, shared across all artillery assets. 0 disables replacement.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Writes Combat Support diagnostic logging to the RPT (CAS engagements, guided delivery, RTB and the rearm-by-landing cycle).</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_AUDIO">
    <English>Radio Messages (Audio):</English>
    <Chinesesimp>无线电信息（音频）</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_AUDIO_COMMENT">
    <English>Uses audible radio messages for support requests</English>
    <Chinesesimp>使用音频无线电信息请求支持</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_TRANS_LIMIT">
    <English>Transport Respawn Limit:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>运输支援限额</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_RESPAWN_COMMENT">
    <English>Time before a destroyed CAS, Transport or Artillery asset is replaced.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_RESPAWN">
    <English>Respawn Time:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>支援间隔时间</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_ALLOW_COMMENT">
    <English>Pick one or more equipment categories. The player can call in Combat Support if they carry any item from any ticked category (e.g. Laser Designators covers vanilla and mod-supplied designator classes). Categories from unloaded mods drop off the list automatically. Defaults to Laser Designators. For mod-supplied items that don't belong to a registered category, use the Custom Access Items (classnames) field below to add their classnames directly.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_ERROR1">
    <English>Only one Combat Support module can be used</English>
    <Chinesesimp>只能使用一个作战支持模块</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_USAGE">
    <English>Place the module and sync it to SUP CAS, SUP Transport and/or SUP Artillery modules.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_SINGLEOP">
    <English>Support Access:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_SINGLEOP_COMMENT">
    <English>Who may call combat support from the tablet. 'First player only' (default) restricts it to a single operator per side; if that player leaves the game, the slot passes to another player automatically. 'All players' gives every player the support tablet.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_CS_NOTOPERATOR">
    <English>You are not the assigned Combat Support operator.</English>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
