<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR">
    <English>Player Command/Control (C2ISTAR)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MENU">
    <English>Player C2ISTAR</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COMMANDER">
    <English>Commander Actions</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COMMENT">
    <English>Command, Control, Comms, Intelligence, Surveillance, Target Acquisition and Reconnaissance</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables verbose C2ISTAR diagnostic output to the RPT log plus extra map markers for generated task targets, civic-state evaluations, and intel coverage decisions. Intended for mission-makers troubleshooting task generation or intel pipeline behaviour.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_ALLOW">
    <English>Required Items:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_ALLOW_COMMENT">
    <English>Pick one or more equipment categories. The player can access C2ISTAR functions if they carry any item from any ticked category (e.g. Laser Designators covers vanilla and mod-supplied designator classes). Categories from unloaded mods drop off the list automatically. Defaults to Laser Designators.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_PERSISTENT">
    <English>Persistent Tasks:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_PERSISTENT_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables external Database persistence for C2ISTAR player tasks</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR">
    <English>Auto Task BLU:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls how the AI commander generates tasks for BLUFOR players.\n\n• None — no auto-generated tasks for BLUFOR.\n• Strategic — tasks pull from OPCOM objectives and recent battlefield events; targets and locations follow OPCOM strategic priorities.\n• Constant — tasks generate on a steady cadence regardless of OPCOM state; useful when no OPCOM is synced or for sandbox missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task BLU Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The friendly faction for BLUFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_ENEMY_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task BLU Enemy Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_ENEMY_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The enemy faction for BLUFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR">
    <English>Auto Task OPF:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls how the AI commander generates tasks for OPFOR players.\n\n• None — no auto-generated tasks for OPFOR.\n• Strategic — tasks pull from OPCOM objectives and recent battlefield events; targets and locations follow OPCOM strategic priorities.\n• Constant — tasks generate on a steady cadence regardless of OPCOM state; useful when no OPCOM is synced or for sandbox missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task OPF Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The friendly faction for OPFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_ENEMY_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task OPF Enemy Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_ENEMY_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The enemy faction for OPFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR">
    <English>Auto Task IND:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls how the AI commander generates tasks for INDFOR players.\n\n• None — no auto-generated tasks for INDFOR.\n• Strategic — tasks pull from OPCOM objectives and recent battlefield events; targets and locations follow OPCOM strategic priorities.\n• Constant — tasks generate on a steady cadence regardless of OPCOM state; useful when no OPCOM is synced or for sandbox missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task IND Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The friendly faction for INDFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_ENEMY_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task IND Enemy Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_ENEMY_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The enemy faction for INDFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT">
    <English>Limit Group Management:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Restricts which groups appear in the player's Group Management list.\n\n• Side — only groups on the same side as the player.\n• Faction — only groups whose faction classname matches the player's faction.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT_SIDE">
    <English>Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT_FACTION">
    <English>Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT">
    <English>Limit Command:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Restricts which forces a player commander can act on via the Operations tablet (spectate, remote-control, image intelligence).\n\n• Side — forces on the same side as the commander.\n• Faction — forces whose faction matches the commander's faction.\n• All — every force the commander can locate, regardless of side or faction.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_SIDE">
    <English>Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_FACTION">
    <English>Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_ALL">
    <English>All</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_SPECTATE">
    <English>Allow Spectate:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_SPECTATE_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow commanders to spectate remote forces</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_JOIN">
    <English>Allow Join:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_JOIN_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow commanders to join remote forces via remote control</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_IMAGE_INTELLIGENCE">
    <English>Allow IMINT:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_IMAGE_INTELLIGENCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow commanders to view live feed from friendly air units</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT">
    <English>Limit Intel:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Restricts which intel a player commander receives via the Intel tablet.\n\n• Side — intel sourced from forces on the same side as the commander.\n• Faction — intel sourced from forces whose faction matches the commander's faction.\n• All — intel from every force, regardless of side or faction.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_SIDE">
    <English>Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_FACTION">
    <English>Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_ALL">
    <English>All</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_INTEL">
    <English>Display Map Intel:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_INTEL_COMMENT">
    <English>Master switch for C2ISTAR map intel. When On, displays mission-wide battlefield events (kills, logistics activity, OPCOM state changes) as markers on the player map. When Off, both intel pipelines shut down — the event listener doesn't register and the OPCOM-side G2 spotrep pump doesn't run, so no markers appear from either source. Combine with Map Intel Visibility to narrow which players see the markers when On.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY">
    <English>Map Intel Visibility:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls which players see C2ISTAR map intel sourced from OPCOM events.\n\n• Same Side — only players on the same side as the reporting OPCOM.\n• Same Faction — only players whose unit faction matches the reporting OPCOM's faction.\n• Friendly Sides — players on any side allied to the reporting OPCOM (side allegiance is per-mission, see sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility settings).\n• All Players — every player, regardless of side.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_SIDE">
    <English>Same Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_FACTION">
    <English>Same Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_FRIENDLY">
    <English>Friendly Sides</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_ALL">
    <English>All Players</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_REVEAL_INSTALLATIONS">
    <English>Reveal Asymmetric Installations:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_REVEAL_INSTALLATIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>When enabled, C2ISTAR map intel can show exact asymmetric OPCOM installation markers. Disabled by default to avoid revealing insurgency infrastructure.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SPOTREP_DIARY_ENTRIES">
    <English>Spotrep Diary Entries:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SPOTREP_DIARY_ENTRIES_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow diary entries when creating Spotreps</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE">
    <English>Intel Coverage:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Amount of intel reports generated</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_OFF">
    <English>Off (0%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_LOW">
    <English>Low (10%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_MEDIUM">
    <English>Medium (20%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_HIGH">
    <English>High (40%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_VERY_HIGH">
    <English>Very High (80%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_TOTAL">
    <English>Total (100%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL">
    <English>Friendly Coverage:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL_COMMENT">
    <English>Display nearby friendly units</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_OPCOM_INTEL_SIDES">
    <English>Commander Intel Sides:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_OPCOM_INTEL_SIDES_COMMENT">
    <English>Selects which synced OPCOM modules feed their G2 spotrep pipeline into C2ISTAR. Comma-separated side keywords: East, West, Independent. Leave blank to disable per-OPCOM intel pumping. Map-marker visibility is separately controlled by Display Map Intel and Map Intel Visibility.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL_RADIUS">
    <English>Friendly Radius (m):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL_RADIUS_COMMENT">
    <English>Display friendly units within this radius around players</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_MIL_SECTORS">
    <English>Military Map Sectors:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_MIL_SECTORS_COMMENT">
    <English>Display map sectors containing military units on the map</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_TRACEGRID">
    <English>T.R.A.C.E System:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_TRACEGRID_COMMENT">
    <English>Renders a 50m by 50m marker grid layer over built-up areas indicating zones of potential (not confirmed) enemy presence. Grid cells change to green when cleared. Select the hatch pattern used for the marker fill.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_PLAYER_SECTORS">
    <English>Player Map Sectors:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_PLAYER_SECTORS_COMMENT">
    <English>Display map sectors containing players on the map</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_RUN_EVERY">
    <English>Sector Update Time (mins):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_RUN_EVERY_COMMENT">
    <English>How often the sector / friendly / military / T.R.A.C.E. map markers refresh, in minutes. Lower values give fresher intel at higher CPU cost. Default 2 minutes.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_USAGE">
    <!-- Translations for other languages pending end-of-module-overhaul translation pass; USAGE text was inaccurate prior (told mission-makers not to sync, but the intel / G2 spotrep pipeline requires each intel-consuming OPCOM to be synced to this module). -->
    <English>Place the C2ISTAR module in the editor and sync it to each AI Commander that should receive intel (spotreps, map markers, G2 reports). Commanders whose side appears in the Commander Intel Sides attribute get their intel pipeline initialised through this sync. Players require a laser designator (by default) in their inventory to access the functions from the ALiVE Action Menu. The required item can be changed in the module settings, for example the alive_tablet, which can be found in a standard support crate.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FILTER_ENEMY_FACTIONS">
    <English>Filter Enemy Factions:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FILTER_ENEMY_FACTIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>When enabled, the Task Enemy Faction list in Generate Task only shows factions actively used by OPCOM modules in this mission. Disable to show all CfgFactionClasses entries.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_MODE">
    <English>Custom Class Mode:</English>
    <Chinese>自訂類別模式：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义类别模式：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Modo de clases personalizadas:</Spanish>
    <French>Mode classes personnalisées:</French>
    <Portuguese>Modo de classes personalizadas:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Режим пользовательских классов:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_MODE_COMMENT">
    <English>How the custom task list below merges into the global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks registry. Replace (default) overwrites the registry with the user-supplied list — matches the legacy init.sqf pattern of assigning ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] directly. Append keeps the existing entries and adds the user-supplied list on top, deduped — useful when extending the stock list with mod-defined task types without losing the defaults. WARNING: legacy assignments to ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks in init.sqf / staticData.sqf execute AFTER module init and silently overwrite this setting. Use either the Eden picker or legacy init-time assignment, not both.</English>
    <Chinese>下方自訂任務清單如何合併進全域 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 註冊表。取代（預設）以使用者提供的清單覆蓋註冊表 — 與舊式於 init.sqf 直接指派 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] 的模式相符。附加保留既有項目,並在其上加入使用者提供的清單並去重 — 適合在擴充原始清單時加入模組定義的任務類型,而不失去預設值。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>下方自定义任务清单如何合并进全局 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 注册表。取代（默认）以用户提供的清单覆盖注册表 — 与旧式于 init.sqf 直接指派 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] 的模式相符。附加保留既有项目,并在其上加入用户提供的清单并去重 — 适合在扩充原始清单时加入模组定义的任务类型,而不失去默认值。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Cómo se combina la lista de tareas personalizadas con el registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (predeterminado) sobrescribe el registro con la lista proporcionada — equivale al patrón heredado de asignar ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] en init.sqf. Append conserva las entradas existentes y añade encima la lista proporcionada, deduplicada — útil para ampliar la lista estándar con tipos de tarea de mods sin perder los valores predeterminados.</Spanish>
    <French>Comment la liste de tâches personnalisées ci-dessous fusionne avec le registre global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (par défaut) écrase le registre avec la liste fournie — équivalent au modèle hérité d'assignation directe ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] dans init.sqf. Append conserve les entrées existantes et ajoute la liste fournie par-dessus, dédupliquée — utile pour étendre la liste standard avec des types de tâches de mods sans perdre les valeurs par défaut.</French>
    <Portuguese>Como a lista de tarefas personalizadas abaixo se mescla com o registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (padrão) sobrescreve o registro com a lista fornecida — equivale ao padrão herdado de atribuir ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] diretamente em init.sqf. Append mantém as entradas existentes e adiciona a lista fornecida em cima, deduplicada — útil para estender a lista padrão com tipos de tarefa de mods sem perder os valores padrão.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Как список пользовательских задач ниже объединяется с глобальным реестром ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (по умолчанию) перезаписывает реестр переданным списком — соответствует прежнему шаблону присваивания ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] в init.sqf. Append сохраняет существующие записи и добавляет переданный список сверху с дедупликацией — полезно для расширения стандартного списка модовыми типами задач без потери значений по умолчанию.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_AUTOGEN_TASKS">
    <English>Override Auto-Generated Tasks:</English>
    <Chinese>覆寫自動生成任務：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>覆写自动生成任务：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Override tareas autogeneradas:</Spanish>
    <French>Override tâches auto-générées:</French>
    <Portuguese>Override tarefas autogeradas:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Перекрыть автогенерируемые задачи:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_AUTOGEN_TASKS_COMMENT">
    <English>Override the global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks registry — the pool of task types the AI commander draws from when auto-generating tasks for players. Tick task types from the listbox to keep them in the override set; type extra mod task types into the Override field with comma-separated names. Replace mode wipes the registry with your selection (the commander only generates the picked tasks); Append mode adds your selection on top of the stock list. Multi-select: left-click selects one row; Ctrl+left-click toggles individual rows; Shift+left-click selects a range.</English>
    <Chinese>覆寫全域 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 註冊表 — AI 指揮官為玩家自動生成任務時所從中抽取的任務類型池。在列表框中勾選要保留於覆寫集中的任務類型;在「覆寫」欄位以逗號分隔輸入額外的模組任務類型。取代模式會以您的選擇清除註冊表(指揮官僅生成所選任務);附加模式則在原始清單之上加入您的選擇。多選:左鍵點擊選取單一項目;Ctrl+左鍵點擊切換個別項目;Shift+左鍵點擊選取範圍。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>覆写全局 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 注册表 — AI 指挥官为玩家自动生成任务时所从中抽取的任务类型池。在列表框中勾选要保留于覆写集中的任务类型;在「覆写」字段以逗号分隔输入额外的模组任务类型。取代模式会以您的选择清除注册表(指挥官仅生成所选任务);附加模式则在原始清单之上加入您的选择。多选:左键点击选取单一项目;Ctrl+左键点击切换个别项目;Shift+左键点击选取范围。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Sobrescribe el registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — el pool de tipos de tarea del que el comandante IA extrae al autogenerar tareas para los jugadores. Marca tipos de tarea en el listbox para mantenerlos en el conjunto override; introduce tipos de tarea de mods adicionales en el campo Override con nombres separados por comas. El modo Replace borra el registro con tu selección (el comandante solo genera las tareas seleccionadas); el modo Append añade tu selección encima de la lista estándar. Selección múltiple: clic izquierdo selecciona una fila; Ctrl+clic izquierdo alterna filas individuales; Shift+clic izquierdo selecciona un rango.</Spanish>
    <French>Surcharge le registre global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — le vivier de types de tâches dans lequel le commandant IA puise pour auto-générer des tâches pour les joueurs. Cochez des types de tâches dans la liste pour les conserver dans l'ensemble override; saisissez des types de tâches de mods supplémentaires dans le champ Override avec des noms séparés par des virgules. Le mode Replace efface le registre avec votre sélection (le commandant ne génère que les tâches choisies); le mode Append ajoute votre sélection par-dessus la liste standard. Sélection multiple : clic gauche sélectionne une ligne ; Ctrl+clic gauche active/désactive des lignes individuelles ; Shift+clic gauche sélectionne une plage.</French>
    <Portuguese>Substitui o registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — o pool de tipos de tarefa do qual o comandante IA extrai ao auto-gerar tarefas para os jogadores. Marque tipos de tarefa no listbox para mantê-los no conjunto override; insira tipos de tarefa de mods adicionais no campo Override com nomes separados por vírgulas. O modo Replace apaga o registro com a sua seleção (o comandante só gera as tarefas escolhidas); o modo Append adiciona a sua seleção sobre a lista padrão. Seleção múltipla: clique esquerdo seleciona uma linha; Ctrl+clique esquerdo alterna linhas individuais; Shift+clique esquerdo seleciona um intervalo.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Перекрывает глобальный реестр ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — пул типов задач, из которого ИИ-командир черпает при автогенерации задач для игроков. Отмечайте типы задач в списке, чтобы сохранить их в наборе override; вводите дополнительные модовые типы задач в поле Override через запятую. Режим Replace стирает реестр и заменяет его вашим выбором (командир генерирует только выбранные задачи); режим Append добавляет ваш выбор поверх стокового списка. Множественный выбор: левый клик выбирает одну строку; Ctrl+левый клик переключает отдельные строки; Shift+левый клик выбирает диапазон.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_MIN_DISTANCE">
    <English>Minimum Task Distance (m):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_MIN_DISTANCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Mission-wide minimum travel distance from the player when picking auto-generated Short / Medium / Long task locations. Set to 0 to disable.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_VIP_PANIC_TIMEOUT">
    <English>VIP Panic Timeout (s):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_VIP_PANIC_TIMEOUT_COMMENT">
    <English>How long, in seconds, a panicked VIP may remain uncontrolled before the VIP Escort task is marked failed.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_AO_RADIUS">
    <English>Task AO Radius (m):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_AO_RADIUS_COMMENT">
    <English>Radius in metres of an optional ellipse marker drawn around each task position to highlight the search area. 0 disables (no circle drawn). Helps players locate task objectives in cluttered terrain where the standard task icon alone is hard to spot. Applies to all auto- and player-generated task markers.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_ENABLED">
    <English>Enable Civic-State COIN Model:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_ENABLED_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables the multi-axis trust / security / services settlement model behind Hearts and Minds tasking. When ON: full 10-task family available (adds Medical Outreach, Checkpoint Partnership, Informant Exfiltration, Market Reopening on top of the legacy 6); per-cluster support state tracked across success / failure / retaliation events; cluster picker prefers settlements with rising insurgent pressure. When OFF: only the 6 legacy families spawn (Aid Delivery, Supply Convoy, Meet Local Leader, VIP Escort, Secure Community Event, Repair Critical Service); simpler success / failure scoring; cluster picker sorts purely by distance. Toggle this BEFORE picking entries in the multi-selects below - the listboxes filter their visible options based on this setting (re-open the attribute panel after toggling to refresh).</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_SUCCESS">
    <English>Trust Success Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_SUCCESS_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to trust gains from successful Hearts and Minds tasks. 1.0 = stock; 2.0 = double; 0.5 = half. Affects how quickly local trust ramps in response to player effort.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_FAILURE">
    <English>Trust Failure Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_FAILURE_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to trust losses from failed Hearts and Minds tasks or insurgent backlash events. Higher values make trust loss more punishing.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_SUCCESS">
    <English>Security Success Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_SUCCESS_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to security gains from successful Hearts and Minds tasks. Security feeds OPCOM hostility decay and insurgent-spawn suppression in settled areas.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_FAILURE">
    <English>Security Failure Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_FAILURE_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to security losses from failed Hearts and Minds tasks or insurgent backlash events.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_SUCCESS">
    <English>Services Success Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_SUCCESS_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to services gains from successful Hearts and Minds tasks. Services represent functioning infrastructure and feed civilian-population cooperation events.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_FAILURE">
    <English>Services Failure Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_FAILURE_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to services losses from failed Hearts and Minds tasks or backlash events.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_COOLDOWN">
    <English>Civic Cooldown Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_COOLDOWN_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to Hearts and Minds task cooldown timers for the civic-state model. Higher values make a settlement wait longer between civic task offers.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DUP_PENALTY">
    <English>Duplicate Task Penalty (0-1):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DUP_PENALTY_COMMENT">
    <English>Penalty strength applied when the same Hearts and Minds task type repeats in the same settlement. Range 0-1; default 0.15 = 15% reward reduction per recent repeat.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_FAMILIES">
    <English>Enabled Civic Task Families:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_FAMILIES_COMMENT">
    <English>Pick one or more Hearts-and-Minds task families that civic-state generation may produce. Untick a family to exclude it from the generation pool. The Override field accepts free-text mod-defined task ids the listbox doesn't surface.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_WEIGHTS">
    <English>Civic Task Weights:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_WEIGHTS_COMMENT">
    <English>Comma-separated TaskType=Weight pairs used by civic-state task selection (no spaces). Higher weights make a task type more likely to be picked. Long string — edit in an external editor and paste.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DEBUG_INTEL">
    <English>Show Civic Debug Intel:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DEBUG_INTEL_COMMENT">
    <English>Appends civic-state trust / security / services summaries to the description text of generated Hearts and Minds tasks. Useful for mission-maker tuning; turn off for player-facing missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_FACTIONS">
    <English>Auto Task Factions:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_FACTIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>Picks one faction per slot for the six per-side auto-task lanes (BLU Friendly / BLU Enemy / OPF Friendly / OPF Enemy / IND Friendly / IND Enemy). Click Next &gt; on the top filter row to cycle through the slots; the listbox shows the faction currently assigned to that slot. The bottom filter row cycles between Auto (narrows the listbox to the slot's natural side) and All (every military faction visible).</English>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
