<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR">
    <English>Player Command/Control (C2ISTAR)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MENU">
    <English>Player C2ISTAR</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COMMANDER">
    <English>Commander Actions</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COMMENT">
    <English>Command, Control, Comms, Intelligence, Surveillance, Target Acquisition and Reconnaissance</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables verbose C2ISTAR diagnostic output to the RPT log plus extra map markers for generated task targets, civic-state evaluations, and intel coverage decisions. Intended for mission-makers troubleshooting task generation or intel pipeline behaviour.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_ALLOW">
    <English>Access Item Categories:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_ALLOW_COMMENT">
    <English>Pick one or more equipment categories. The player can access C2ISTAR functions if they carry any item from any ticked category (e.g. Laser Designators covers vanilla and mod-supplied designator classes). Categories from unloaded mods drop off the list automatically. Defaults to Laser Designators. For mod-supplied items that don't belong to a registered category, use the Custom Access Items (classnames) field below to add their classnames directly.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CUSTOM_ITEMS">
    <English>Custom Access Items (classnames):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CUSTOM_ITEMS_COMMENT">
    <English>Comma-separated list of additional item classnames that should grant C2ISTAR access on top of the Access Item Categories above. Use this for mod-supplied items that don't fit a registered category (e.g. a custom faction's command tablet, a campaign-specific intel device). Classnames are matched literally and case-insensitively against the player's assigned items / uniform / vest / backpack. Example: "MyMod_CommandTablet, AnotherMod_FieldRadio". Leave empty for none.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_PERSISTENT">
    <English>Persistent Tasks:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_PERSISTENT_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables external Database persistence for C2ISTAR player tasks</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR">
    <English>Auto Task BLU:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls how the AI commander generates tasks for BLUFOR players.\n\n• None — no auto-generated tasks for BLUFOR.\n• Strategic — tasks pull from OPCOM objectives and recent battlefield events; targets and locations follow OPCOM strategic priorities.\n• Constant — tasks generate on a steady cadence regardless of OPCOM state; useful when no OPCOM is synced or for sandbox missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task BLU Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The friendly faction for BLUFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_ENEMY_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task BLU Enemy Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_BLUFOR_ENEMY_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The enemy faction for BLUFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR">
    <English>Auto Task OPF:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls how the AI commander generates tasks for OPFOR players.\n\n• None — no auto-generated tasks for OPFOR.\n• Strategic — tasks pull from OPCOM objectives and recent battlefield events; targets and locations follow OPCOM strategic priorities.\n• Constant — tasks generate on a steady cadence regardless of OPCOM state; useful when no OPCOM is synced or for sandbox missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task OPF Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The friendly faction for OPFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_ENEMY_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task OPF Enemy Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_OPFOR_ENEMY_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The enemy faction for OPFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR">
    <English>Auto Task IND:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls how the AI commander generates tasks for INDFOR players.\n\n• None — no auto-generated tasks for INDFOR.\n• Strategic — tasks pull from OPCOM objectives and recent battlefield events; targets and locations follow OPCOM strategic priorities.\n• Constant — tasks generate on a steady cadence regardless of OPCOM state; useful when no OPCOM is synced or for sandbox missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task IND Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The friendly faction for INDFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_ENEMY_FACTION">
    <English>Auto Task IND Enemy Faction:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_INDFOR_ENEMY_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>The enemy faction for INDFOR task autogeneration</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT">
    <English>Limit Group Management:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Restricts which groups appear in the player's Group Management list.\n\n• Side — only groups on the same side as the player.\n• Faction — only groups whose faction classname matches the player's faction.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT_SIDE">
    <English>Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_GM_LIMIT_FACTION">
    <English>Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT">
    <English>Limit Command:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Restricts which forces a player commander can act on via the Operations tablet (spectate, remote-control, image intelligence).\n\n• Side — forces on the same side as the commander.\n• Faction — forces whose faction matches the commander's faction.\n• All — every force the commander can locate, regardless of side or faction.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_SIDE">
    <English>Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_FACTION">
    <English>Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_LIMIT_ALL">
    <English>All</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_SPECTATE">
    <English>Allow Spectate:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_SPECTATE_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow commanders to spectate remote forces</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_JOIN">
    <English>Allow Join:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_JOIN_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow commanders to join remote forces via remote control</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_ALLOW_IMAGE_INTELLIGENCE">
    <English>Allow IMINT:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_OPS_IMAGE_INTELLIGENCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow commanders to view live feed from friendly air units</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT">
    <English>Limit Intel:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Restricts which intel a player commander receives via the Intel tablet.\n\n• Side — intel sourced from forces on the same side as the commander.\n• Faction — intel sourced from forces whose faction matches the commander's faction.\n• All — intel from every force, regardless of side or faction.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_SIDE">
    <English>Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_FACTION">
    <English>Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SCOM_INTEL_LIMIT_ALL">
    <English>All</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_INTEL">
    <English>Display Map Intel:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_INTEL_COMMENT">
    <English>Master switch for C2ISTAR map intel. When On, displays mission-wide battlefield events (kills, logistics activity, OPCOM state changes) as markers on the player map. When Off, both intel pipelines shut down — the event listener doesn't register and the OPCOM-side G2 spotrep pump doesn't run, so no markers appear from either source. Combine with Map Intel Visibility to narrow which players see the markers when On. INTERACTION WITH COP: when Commander Intel Mode (further down) is on, the basic NATO chevron spotrep markers from this layer are auto-suppressed to avoid duplicating COP's per-frame enemy rendering. The TACOM Recon / Capture blocking-line markers (FLOT rectangles + advance arrows) continue to render alongside COP — set this attribute Yes if you want those blocking lines on top of the COP overlay.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY">
    <English>Map Intel Visibility:</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls which players see C2ISTAR map intel. Covers both OPCOM-sourced intel (G2 spotrep events from the OPCOM-side pipeline, gated by Commander Intel Sides) and profile-system events (PROFILE_KILLED, IED detonations, civilian agent kills) which fire independently of OPCOM sync. This is a RECIPIENT filter — composes with Commander Intel Sides (source filter): only intel from the picked OPCOM sides reaches C2ISTAR, then this filter decides which players see those markers.\n\n• Same Side — only players on the same side as the reporting OPCOM.\n• Same Faction — only players whose unit faction matches the reporting OPCOM's faction.\n• Friendly Sides — players on any side allied to the reporting OPCOM (side allegiance is per-mission, see sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility settings).\n• All Players — every player, regardless of side.</English>
    <Chinese>控制哪些玩家能看到 C2ISTAR 地圖情報。涵蓋來自 OPCOM 的情報(來自 OPCOM-side 管線的 G2 spotrep 事件,由 Commander Intel Sides 控制)以及 profile 系統事件(PROFILE_KILLED、IED 引爆、平民代理人擊殺),後者獨立於 OPCOM 同步觸發。此為接收者過濾器 — 與 Commander Intel Sides(來源過濾器)組合運作:只有來自所選 OPCOM 陣營的情報能到達 C2ISTAR,然後此過濾器決定哪些玩家能看到這些標記。\n\n• Same Side — 僅與回報 OPCOM 同一陣營的玩家。\n• Same Faction — 僅單位陣營(faction)與回報 OPCOM 之 faction 相符的玩家。\n• Friendly Sides — 與回報 OPCOM 結盟之任何陣營的玩家(陣營結盟為每任務設定,參見 sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility 設定)。\n• All Players — 所有玩家,不分陣營。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>控制哪些玩家能看到 C2ISTAR 地图情报。涵盖来自 OPCOM 的情报(来自 OPCOM-side 管线的 G2 spotrep 事件,由 Commander Intel Sides 控制)以及 profile 系统事件(PROFILE_KILLED、IED 引爆、平民代理人击杀),后者独立于 OPCOM 同步触发。此为接收者过滤器 — 与 Commander Intel Sides(来源过滤器)组合运作:只有来自所选 OPCOM 阵营的情报能到达 C2ISTAR,然后此过滤器决定哪些玩家能看到这些标记。\n\n• Same Side — 仅与回报 OPCOM 同一阵营的玩家。\n• Same Faction — 仅单位阵营(faction)与回报 OPCOM 之 faction 相符的玩家。\n• Friendly Sides — 与回报 OPCOM 结盟之任何阵营的玩家(阵营结盟为每任务设定,参见 sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility 设定)。\n• All Players — 所有玩家,不分阵营。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Controla qué jugadores ven la intel de mapa de C2ISTAR. Cubre tanto la intel de fuente OPCOM (eventos G2 spotrep del pipeline OPCOM-side, filtrados por Commander Intel Sides) como los eventos del sistema profile (PROFILE_KILLED, detonaciones de IED, kills de agentes civiles) que se disparan independientemente del sync de OPCOM. Esto es un filtro de DESTINATARIO — se compone con Commander Intel Sides (filtro de fuente): solo la intel de los bandos OPCOM elegidos llega a C2ISTAR, y entonces este filtro decide qué jugadores ven esos marcadores.\n\n• Same Side — solo jugadores del mismo bando que el OPCOM informante.\n• Same Faction — solo jugadores cuya faction de unidad coincida con la faction del OPCOM informante.\n• Friendly Sides — jugadores de cualquier bando aliado del OPCOM informante (la afinidad de bando es por misión, ver ajustes de sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility).\n• All Players — todos los jugadores, sin importar el bando.</Spanish>
    <French>Contrôle quels joueurs voient l'intel de carte C2ISTAR. Couvre à la fois l'intel de source OPCOM (événements G2 spotrep du pipeline OPCOM-side, filtrés par Commander Intel Sides) et les événements du système profile (PROFILE_KILLED, détonations d'IED, kills d'agents civils) qui se déclenchent indépendamment du sync OPCOM. Ceci est un filtre de DESTINATAIRE — se compose avec Commander Intel Sides (filtre de source) : seule l'intel des camps OPCOM sélectionnés atteint C2ISTAR, puis ce filtre décide quels joueurs voient ces marqueurs.\n\n• Same Side — uniquement les joueurs du même camp que l'OPCOM rapporteur.\n• Same Faction — uniquement les joueurs dont la faction d'unité correspond à la faction de l'OPCOM rapporteur.\n• Friendly Sides — les joueurs de tout camp allié de l'OPCOM rapporteur (l'allégeance de camp est par mission, voir les réglages sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility).\n• All Players — chaque joueur, quel que soit le camp.</French>
    <Portuguese>Controla quais jogadores veem a intel de mapa do C2ISTAR. Cobre tanto a intel de fonte OPCOM (eventos G2 spotrep do pipeline OPCOM-side, filtrados por Commander Intel Sides) quanto os eventos do sistema profile (PROFILE_KILLED, detonações de IED, kills de agentes civis) que disparam independentemente do sync de OPCOM. Este é um filtro de DESTINATÁRIO — compõe-se com Commander Intel Sides (filtro de fonte): somente a intel dos lados OPCOM escolhidos chega ao C2ISTAR, e então este filtro decide quais jogadores veem esses marcadores.\n\n• Same Side — somente jogadores do mesmo lado que o OPCOM relator.\n• Same Faction — somente jogadores cuja faction de unidade coincide com a faction do OPCOM relator.\n• Friendly Sides — jogadores de qualquer lado aliado ao OPCOM relator (a aliança de lado é por missão, veja configurações de sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility).\n• All Players — todo jogador, independente do lado.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Контролирует, какие игроки видят карт-интел C2ISTAR. Охватывает как интел из источника OPCOM (события G2 spotrep из конвейера OPCOM-side, отфильтрованные через Commander Intel Sides), так и события системы profile (PROFILE_KILLED, подрывы IED, убийства гражданских агентов), которые срабатывают независимо от синка OPCOM. Это фильтр ПОЛУЧАТЕЛЯ — комбинируется с Commander Intel Sides (фильтр источника): только интел из выбранных сторон OPCOM достигает C2ISTAR, а затем этот фильтр решает, какие игроки видят эти маркеры.\n\n• Same Side — только игроки той же стороны, что и рапортующий OPCOM.\n• Same Faction — только игроки, чья faction юнита совпадает с faction рапортующего OPCOM.\n• Friendly Sides — игроки любой стороны, союзной рапортующему OPCOM (принадлежность стороны задаётся per-mission, см. настройки sys_aiskill / OPCOM hostility).\n• All Players — каждый игрок, независимо от стороны.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_SIDE">
    <English>Same Side</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_FACTION">
    <English>Same Faction</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_FRIENDLY">
    <English>Friendly Sides</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_VISIBILITY_ALL">
    <English>All Players</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_REVEAL_INSTALLATIONS">
    <English>Reveal Asymmetric Installations:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_MAP_INTEL_REVEAL_INSTALLATIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>When enabled, C2ISTAR map intel can show exact asymmetric OPCOM installation markers. Disabled by default to avoid revealing insurgency infrastructure.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SPOTREP_DIARY_ENTRIES">
    <English>Spotrep Diary Entries:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_SPOTREP_DIARY_ENTRIES_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow diary entries when creating Spotreps</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE">
    <English>Intel Coverage:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Amount of intel reports generated</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_OFF">
    <English>Off (0%)</English>
    <Chinese>關閉 (0%)</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>关闭 (0%)</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Desactivado (0%)</Spanish>
    <French>Désactivé (0%)</French>
    <Portuguese>Desativado (0%)</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Выкл (0%)</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_LOW">
    <English>Low (10%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_MEDIUM">
    <English>Medium (20%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_HIGH">
    <English>High (40%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_VERY_HIGH">
    <English>Very High (80%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_INTEL_CHANCE_TOTAL">
    <English>Total (100%)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL">
    <English>Friendly Coverage:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL_COMMENT">
    <English>Display nearby friendly units</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_OPCOM_INTEL_SIDES">
    <English>Commander Intel Sides:</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_OPCOM_INTEL_SIDES_COMMENT">
    <English>Selects which synced OPCOM modules feed their G2 spotrep pipeline into C2ISTAR. Tick one or more sides (East, West, Independent); leave all unticked to disable per-OPCOM intel pumping. This is a SOURCE filter — controls which OPCOMs flow intel in. Map-marker visibility (which players see the resulting markers) is separately controlled by Display Map Intel and Map Intel Visibility.</English>
    <Chinese>選擇哪些已同步的 OPCOM 模組將其 G2 spotrep 管線匯入 C2ISTAR。勾選一個或多個陣營(East、West、Independent);全部不勾選即停用 per-OPCOM 情報匯入。此為來源過濾器 — 控制哪些 OPCOM 匯入情報。地圖標記的可見性(哪些玩家能看到產生的標記)由 Display Map Intel 與 Map Intel Visibility 另行控制。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>选择哪些已同步的 OPCOM 模组将其 G2 spotrep 管线汇入 C2ISTAR。勾选一个或多个阵营(East、West、Independent);全部不勾选即停用 per-OPCOM 情报汇入。此为来源过滤器 — 控制哪些 OPCOM 汇入情报。地图标记的可见性(哪些玩家能看到产生的标记)由 Display Map Intel 与 Map Intel Visibility 另行控制。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Selecciona qué módulos OPCOM sincronizados alimentan su pipeline de G2 spotrep a C2ISTAR. Marca uno o más bandos (East, West, Independent); déjalos todos sin marcar para deshabilitar el bombeo de intel por OPCOM. Esto es un filtro de FUENTE — controla qué OPCOMs aportan intel. La visibilidad del marcador de mapa (qué jugadores ven los marcadores resultantes) se controla por separado mediante Display Map Intel y Map Intel Visibility.</Spanish>
    <French>Sélectionne quels modules OPCOM synchronisés alimentent leur pipeline G2 spotrep dans C2ISTAR. Cochez un ou plusieurs camps (East, West, Independent) ; laissez tout décoché pour désactiver le pompage d'intel par OPCOM. Ceci est un filtre de SOURCE — contrôle quels OPCOMs font remonter l'intel. La visibilité des marqueurs de carte (quels joueurs voient les marqueurs résultants) est contrôlée séparément par Display Map Intel et Map Intel Visibility.</French>
    <Portuguese>Seleciona quais módulos OPCOM sincronizados alimentam seu pipeline de G2 spotrep no C2ISTAR. Marque um ou mais lados (East, West, Independent); deixe todos desmarcados para desabilitar o bombeamento de intel por OPCOM. Este é um filtro de FONTE — controla quais OPCOMs alimentam intel. A visibilidade dos marcadores de mapa (quais jogadores veem os marcadores resultantes) é controlada separadamente por Display Map Intel e Map Intel Visibility.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Выбирает, какие синхронизированные модули OPCOM подают свой конвейер G2 spotrep в C2ISTAR. Отметьте одну или несколько сторон (East, West, Independent); оставьте все неотмеченными, чтобы отключить подачу интела по OPCOM. Это фильтр ИСТОЧНИКА — контролирует, какие OPCOM поставляют интел. Видимость карт-маркеров (какие игроки видят итоговые маркеры) контролируется отдельно через Display Map Intel и Map Intel Visibility.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL_RADIUS">
    <English>Friendly Radius (m):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FRIENDLY_INTEL_RADIUS_COMMENT">
    <English>Display friendly units within this radius around players</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_MIL_SECTORS">
    <English>Military Map Sectors:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_MIL_SECTORS_COMMENT">
    <English>Display map sectors containing military units on the map</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_TRACEGRID">
    <English>T.R.A.C.E System:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_TRACEGRID_COMMENT">
    <English>Renders a 50m by 50m marker grid layer over built-up areas indicating zones of potential (not confirmed) enemy presence. Grid cells change to green when cleared. Select the hatch pattern used for the marker fill.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_PLAYER_SECTORS">
    <English>Player Map Sectors:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_DISPLAY_PLAYER_SECTORS_COMMENT">
    <English>Display map sectors containing players on the map</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ENABLE">
    <English>Enable Live Commander Intel (COP):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ENABLE_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables the Common Operational Picture map overlay — a real-time commander-intel layer that complements T.R.A.C.E. The server polls OPCOM data and broadcasts side-filtered enemy intel, friendly force tracking (BFT), commander objectives, and asymmetric activity to clients. Renders on the main map when open. Where T.R.A.C.E simulates ELINT-style potential-presence shading, COP simulates KNOWN intel reports received by the commander from OPCOM.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ENABLE_LEGACY_DEPRECATED">
    <English>DEPRECATED — replaced by Commander Intel Mode. Use the new attribute instead.</English>
    <Chinese>已棄用 — 由「指揮官情報模式」取代。請改用新屬性。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>已弃用 — 由「指挥官情报模式」取代。请改用新属性。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>OBSOLETO — reemplazado por Modo de Inteligencia del Comandante. Use el nuevo atributo en su lugar.</Spanish>
    <French>OBSOLÈTE — remplacé par le Mode d'Intelligence du Commandant. Utilisez le nouvel attribut à la place.</French>
    <Portuguese>OBSOLETO — substituído pelo Modo de Inteligência do Comandante. Use o novo atributo.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>УСТАРЕЛО — заменено на Режим разведданных командира. Используйте новый атрибут.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_MODE">
    <English>Commander Intel Mode (COP):</English>
    <Chinese>指揮官情報模式 (COP):</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>指挥官情报模式 (COP):</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Modo de Inteligencia del Comandante (COP):</Spanish>
    <French>Mode d'Intelligence du Commandant (COP):</French>
    <Portuguese>Modo de Inteligência do Comandante (COP):</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Режим разведданных командира (COP):</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_MODE_COMMENT">
    <English>Off / Basic / Partial / Full / Advanced. Master tier selector for the Common Operational Picture overlay. Off = no COP code runs. Basic = objective circles only (no enemy intel, no BFT). Partial = enemy clusters + objectives, no BFT, no movement vector. Full = enemies + BFT + objectives with baseline features only (no trail / threat ring / confidence border / composition labels). Advanced = full feature set. ENEMY DATA SOURCE: COP reads each conventional mil_opcom module's known-entities cache directly — independent of the Map Intel settings above. To see enemy contacts you need (1) a mil_opcom placed for each side you want intel from, (2) friendly profile-managed forces (mil_placement / sys_profile) so OPCOM has scouts to detect enemies through, and (3) enough mission runtime (10-20 min) for OPCOM patrols to make contact and populate the known-entities cache. Sparse early-cycle data is normal. FRIENDLY (BFT) DATA SOURCE: the friendly layer queries profile-managed units within 8km of each player. If your BLUFOR forces are SQM-placed hosted units (not virtualised by mil_placement / sys_profile), BFT renders empty even at the Advanced tier — same applies to OPFOR/IND. Hosted AI in a player's own group typically aren't profiled either. INTERACTION WITH MAP INTEL: when this is on and Display Map Intel above is also Yes, COP and the Map Intel layer coexist — COP renders enemy contacts and friendly BFT, the Map Intel layer renders TACOM Recon / Capture blocking lines (FLOT rectangles + advance arrows) alongside COP, and the basic NATO chevron spotrep markers are auto-suppressed to avoid duplication. Set Display Map Intel = No to disable the Map Intel layer entirely. Legacy note: if the older enableLiveCommanderIntel attribute is set in init.sqf, the Off value is overridden by it — remove the legacy attribute to fully disable COP.</English>
    <Chinese>關閉 / 基本 / 部分 / 完整 / 進階。共同作戰圖像覆蓋層的主要層級選擇器。關閉 = COP 程式碼不執行。基本 = 僅目標圓圈（無敵情、無 BFT）。部分 = 敵方叢集 + 目標，無 BFT、無移動向量。完整 = 敵方 + BFT + 目標，僅基線功能（無軌跡 / 威脅環 / 信心邊框 / 組成標籤）。進階 = 完整功能集。注意：如果在 init.sqf 中設定了舊版 enableLiveCommanderIntel 屬性，「關閉」值會被它覆寫 — 請移除舊版屬性以完全停用 COP。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>关闭 / 基本 / 部分 / 完整 / 高级。共同作战图像覆盖层的主要层级选择器。关闭 = COP 代码不运行。基本 = 仅目标圆圈（无敌情、无 BFT）。部分 = 敌方集群 + 目标，无 BFT、无移动矢量。完整 = 敌方 + BFT + 目标，仅基线功能（无轨迹 / 威胁环 / 信心边框 / 组成标签）。高级 = 完整功能集。注意：如果在 init.sqf 中设置了旧版 enableLiveCommanderIntel 属性，「关闭」值会被它覆盖 — 请移除旧版属性以完全禁用 COP。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Off / Basic / Partial / Full / Advanced. Selector de nivel maestro para la superposición de Imagen Operativa Común (COP). Off = ningún código COP se ejecuta. Basic = solo círculos de objetivos (sin inteligencia enemiga, sin BFT). Partial = clústeres enemigos + objetivos, sin BFT, sin vector de movimiento. Full = enemigos + BFT + objetivos con solo características básicas (sin rastro / anillo de amenaza / borde de confianza / etiquetas de composición). Advanced = conjunto completo de características. Nota: si el atributo heredado enableLiveCommanderIntel está establecido en init.sqf, el valor Off es anulado por él — elimine el atributo heredado para desactivar COP completamente.</Spanish>
    <French>Off / Basic / Partial / Full / Advanced. Sélecteur de niveau maître pour la superposition de l'Image Opérationnelle Commune (COP). Off = aucun code COP ne s'exécute. Basic = uniquement les cercles d'objectifs (pas de renseignement ennemi, pas de BFT). Partial = clusters ennemis + objectifs, pas de BFT, pas de vecteur de mouvement. Full = ennemis + BFT + objectifs avec uniquement les fonctionnalités de base (pas de traînée / anneau de menace / bordure de confiance / étiquettes de composition). Advanced = ensemble complet de fonctionnalités. Note: si l'attribut hérité enableLiveCommanderIntel est défini dans init.sqf, la valeur Off est remplacée par celui-ci — supprimez l'attribut hérité pour désactiver complètement COP.</French>
    <Portuguese>Off / Basic / Partial / Full / Advanced. Seletor de nível mestre para a sobreposição de Imagem Operacional Comum (COP). Off = nenhum código COP é executado. Basic = apenas círculos de objetivos (sem inteligência inimiga, sem BFT). Partial = clusters inimigos + objetivos, sem BFT, sem vetor de movimento. Full = inimigos + BFT + objetivos apenas com recursos básicos (sem rastro / anel de ameaça / borda de confiança / rótulos de composição). Advanced = conjunto completo de recursos. Nota: se o atributo legado enableLiveCommanderIntel estiver definido em init.sqf, o valor Off é substituído por ele — remova o atributo legado para desativar o COP completamente.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Off / Basic / Partial / Full / Advanced. Главный селектор уровня для наложения Общей оперативной картины (COP). Off = код COP не выполняется. Basic = только круги задач (без разведданных о противнике, без BFT). Partial = кластеры противника + задачи, без BFT, без вектора движения. Full = противники + BFT + задачи только с базовыми функциями (без следа / кольца угрозы / границы достоверности / меток состава). Advanced = полный набор функций. Примечание: если устаревший атрибут enableLiveCommanderIntel установлен в init.sqf, значение Off переопределяется им — удалите устаревший атрибут, чтобы полностью отключить COP.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_MODE_OFF">
    <English>Off</English>
    <Chinese>關閉</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>关闭</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Apagado</Spanish>
    <French>Désactivé</French>
    <Portuguese>Desligado</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Выкл.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_MODE_BASIC">
    <English>Basic</English>
    <Chinese>基本</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>基本</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Básico</Spanish>
    <French>De base</French>
    <Portuguese>Básico</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Базовый</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_MODE_PARTIAL">
    <English>Partial</English>
    <Chinese>部分</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>部分</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Parcial</Spanish>
    <French>Partiel</French>
    <Portuguese>Parcial</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Частичный</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_MODE_FULL">
    <English>Full</English>
    <Chinese>完整</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>完整</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Completo</Spanish>
    <French>Complet</French>
    <Portuguese>Completo</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Полный</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_MODE_ADVANCED">
    <English>Advanced</English>
    <Chinese>進階</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>高级</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Avanzado</Spanish>
    <French>Avancé</French>
    <Portuguese>Avançado</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Расширенный</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ASYM">
    <English>Commander Intel — Asymmetric:</English>
    <Chinese>指揮官情報 — 非對稱:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>指挥官情报 — 非对称:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Inteligencia del Comandante — Asimétrica:</Spanish>
    <French>Intelligence du Commandant — Asymétrique:</French>
    <Portuguese>Inteligência do Comandante — Assimétrica:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Разведданные командира — Асимметричные:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ASYM_COMMENT">
    <English>When Yes, and Commander Intel Mode is not Off, the asymmetric COP layer (Layer 5) runs — insurgent activity zones, civilian sentiment, and infrastructure markers. When No, Layer 5 is forced off regardless of master defaults. Has no effect when Commander Intel Mode is Off. DATA SOURCE: requires an asymmetric OPCOM module (mil_opcom with control type set to "asymmetric") placed in the mission — without one the Asymmetric layer has nothing to display even when this is set to Yes.</English>
    <Chinese>設為「是」且指揮官情報模式不為「關閉」時，非對稱 COP 層（第 5 層）會執行 — 叛亂活動區域、平民情緒和基礎設施標記。設為「否」時，無論主預設為何，第 5 層都會被強制關閉。指揮官情報模式為「關閉」時無效。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>设为「是」且指挥官情报模式不为「关闭」时，非对称 COP 层（第 5 层）会执行 — 叛乱活动区域、平民情绪和基础设施标记。设为「否」时，无论主预设为何，第 5 层都会被强制关闭。指挥官情报模式为「关闭」时无效。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Cuando se establece en Sí y el Modo de Inteligencia del Comandante no es Off, la capa COP asimétrica (Capa 5) se ejecuta — zonas de actividad insurgente, sentimiento civil y marcadores de infraestructura. Cuando se establece en No, la Capa 5 se desactiva forzosamente independientemente de los valores predeterminados. No tiene efecto cuando el Modo de Inteligencia del Comandante es Off.</Spanish>
    <French>Lorsqu'il est défini sur Oui et que le Mode d'Intelligence du Commandant n'est pas Off, la couche COP asymétrique (Couche 5) s'exécute — zones d'activité insurgée, sentiment civil et marqueurs d'infrastructure. Lorsqu'il est défini sur Non, la Couche 5 est forcée à off quels que soient les paramètres par défaut. N'a aucun effet lorsque le Mode d'Intelligence du Commandant est Off.</French>
    <Portuguese>Quando definido como Sim e o Modo de Inteligência do Comandante não for Off, a camada COP assimétrica (Camada 5) é executada — zonas de atividade insurgente, sentimento civil e marcadores de infraestrutura. Quando definido como Não, a Camada 5 é forçadamente desativada independentemente dos padrões mestres. Não tem efeito quando o Modo de Inteligência do Comandante é Off.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>При значении Да и Режиме разведданных командира, отличном от Off, запускается асимметричный слой COP (Слой 5) — зоны повстанческой активности, гражданские настроения и маркеры инфраструктуры. При значении Нет Слой 5 принудительно отключается независимо от мастер-настроек. Не имеет эффекта, когда Режим разведданных командира установлен в Off.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ASYM_YES">
    <English>Yes</English>
    <Chinese>是</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>是</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Sí</Spanish>
    <French>Oui</French>
    <Portuguese>Sim</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Да</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ASYM_NO">
    <English>No</English>
    <Chinese>否</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>否</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>No</Spanish>
    <French>Non</French>
    <Portuguese>Não</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Нет</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_UPDATE_INTERVAL">
    <English>COP Update Interval:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_UPDATE_INTERVAL_COMMENT">
    <English>How often the COP server pulls fresh intel from each OPCOM. Loop A (enemies + BFT) runs at this interval; Loop B (objectives, lower-priority) runs at 2x this value. Upstream OPCOM's TACOM analysis cycle is fixed at 120 seconds — that's the cap on data freshness regardless of how fast COP polls. Presets: Fast (15s, tight feedback for active engagements), Standard (30s, responsive), Balanced (60s, recommended default — half a TACOM cycle, catches every update within 60s for half the redundant work), Economy (120s, aligned with TACOM cycle, cheapest server load). Independent of the Sector Update Time setting above.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_UPDATE_FAST">
    <English>Fast (15s)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_UPDATE_STANDARD">
    <English>Standard (30s)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_UPDATE_BALANCED">
    <English>Balanced (60s)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_UPDATE_ECONOMY">
    <English>Economy (120s)</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_DISPLAY_SIDES">
    <English>COP Display Sides:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_DISPLAY_SIDES_COMMENT">
    <English>Which sides' COP data feeds get rendered on the player's map. Leave EMPTY for the default (player's own side only). Tick additional sides to merge their intel + BFT + objectives into the player's view — useful for a Game Master / commander / observer role who wants to monitor multiple sides at once. Each ticked side requires a placed mil_opcom for its data to populate. Each player still sees only what their own client is configured for; this is a mission-maker filter, not a per-player switch. Independent of Commander Intel Sides above, which gates the legacy spotrep / diary intel.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_SHOW_BFT">
    <English>COP — Friendly BFT:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_SHOW_BFT_COMMENT">
    <English>Toggle the friendly Blue Force Tracker layer in the COP overlay independently of the Commander Intel Mode tier. Yes (default) renders friendly profile-managed forces as side-coloured chevrons within the anchor radius — useful for cooperative play and command overview. No suppresses BFT regardless of tier, even when Commander Intel Mode is Full / Advanced — useful for tighter operational security simulations where players should not see automatic friendly positions on the map. Independent of the Map Intel "Friendly Coverage" setting above, which drives the legacy global SQM friendly markers.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_SHOW_BFT_YES">
    <English>Yes</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_SHOW_BFT_NO">
    <English>No</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ANCHOR_DISTANCE">
    <English>COP Anchor Distance:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_COP_ANCHOR_DISTANCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Radius around each player within which COP intel (enemies, BFT, objectives, asymmetric) is displayed on the map. The anchor is the player — this distance determines how far from the player's position intel appears. This is a RENDER-side setting only; it does not change what intel OPCOM gathers, only what portion of it gets drawn on your map. WARNING: high distances (1000 m or more) combined with many objectives or high unit counts can cause COP to take longer to display information and may reduce client frame rate with the map open.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_RUN_EVERY">
    <English>Sector Update Time (mins):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_RUN_EVERY_COMMENT">
    <English>How often the sector / friendly / military / T.R.A.C.E. map markers refresh, in minutes. Lower values give fresher intel at higher CPU cost. Default 2 minutes.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_USAGE">
    <!-- Translations for other languages pending end-of-module-overhaul translation pass; USAGE text was inaccurate prior (told mission-makers not to sync, but the intel / G2 spotrep pipeline requires each intel-consuming OPCOM to be synced to this module). -->
    <English>Place the C2ISTAR module in the editor and sync it to each AI Commander that should receive intel (spotreps, map markers, G2 reports). Commanders whose side appears in the Commander Intel Sides attribute get their intel pipeline initialised through this sync. Players require a laser designator (by default) in their inventory to access the functions from the ALiVE Action Menu. The required item can be changed in the module settings, for example the alive_tablet, which can be found in a standard support crate.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_USAGE_MARKERS">
    <English>Note on map markers: KIA markers and contact reports can reflect simulated combat between virtualised profiles that never physically spawned. The ALiVE profile simulator resolves engagements off-screen — civilian agents killed by insurgent activity, IED detonations near profile groups, and suicide bombings all surface as map events even when nothing visible is happening in the player's local area. This is expected behaviour, not a bug.</English>
    <Chinese>關於地圖標記的說明:KIA 標記與接觸報告可能反映從未實際生成的虛擬化 profile 之間的模擬戰鬥。ALiVE profile 模擬器在畫面外解算交戰 — 遭叛亂活動殺害的平民代理人、profile 群組附近的 IED 引爆,以及自殺炸彈攻擊,皆會以地圖事件呈現,即使玩家本地區域內並無可見動作發生。此為預期行為,並非錯誤。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>关于地图标记的说明:KIA 标记与接触报告可能反映从未实际生成的虚拟化 profile 之间的模拟战斗。ALiVE profile 模拟器在画面外解算交战 — 遭叛乱活动杀害的平民代理人、profile 群组附近的 IED 引爆,以及自杀炸弹攻击,皆会以地图事件呈现,即使玩家本地区域内并无可见动作发生。此为预期行为,并非错误。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Nota sobre los marcadores de mapa: los marcadores KIA y los informes de contacto pueden reflejar combate simulado entre profiles virtualizados que nunca se han spawneado físicamente. El simulador de profiles de ALiVE resuelve los enfrentamientos fuera de pantalla — agentes civiles muertos por actividad insurgente, detonaciones de IED cerca de grupos profile y atentados suicidas se manifiestan como eventos de mapa incluso cuando no ocurre nada visible en el área local del jugador. Este es el comportamiento esperado, no un bug.</Spanish>
    <French>Note sur les marqueurs de carte : les marqueurs KIA et les rapports de contact peuvent refléter un combat simulé entre profiles virtualisés qui n'ont jamais été spawnés physiquement. Le simulateur de profiles d'ALiVE résout les engagements hors écran — les agents civils tués par l'activité insurgée, les détonations d'IED à proximité de groupes profile et les attentats-suicides apparaissent tous comme des événements de carte même lorsque rien de visible ne se produit dans la zone locale du joueur. Ceci est un comportement attendu, pas un bug.</French>
    <Portuguese>Nota sobre os marcadores de mapa: marcadores KIA e relatórios de contato podem refletir combate simulado entre profiles virtualizados que nunca spawnaram fisicamente. O simulador de profiles do ALiVE resolve os engajamentos fora da tela — agentes civis mortos por atividade insurgente, detonações de IED próximas a grupos profile e atentados suicidas surgem todos como eventos de mapa mesmo quando nada visível está acontecendo na área local do jogador. Este é o comportamento esperado, não um bug.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Примечание о маркерах карты: маркеры KIA и доклады о контакте могут отражать симулированный бой между виртуализированными profile, которые никогда физически не спавнились. Симулятор profile ALiVE разрешает столкновения вне экрана — гражданские агенты, убитые повстанческой деятельностью, подрывы IED вблизи групп profile и атаки смертников — всё это всплывает как события карты, даже когда в локальной зоне игрока ничего видимого не происходит. Это ожидаемое поведение, а не баг.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FILTER_ENEMY_FACTIONS">
    <English>Filter Enemy Factions:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_FILTER_ENEMY_FACTIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>When enabled, the Task Enemy Faction list in Generate Task only shows factions actively used by OPCOM modules in this mission. Disable to show all CfgFactionClasses entries.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_MODE">
    <English>Custom Class Mode:</English>
    <Chinese>自訂類別模式：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>自定义类别模式：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Modo de clases personalizadas:</Spanish>
    <French>Mode classes personnalisées:</French>
    <Portuguese>Modo de classes personalizadas:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Режим пользовательских классов:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_MODE_COMMENT">
    <English>How the custom task list below merges into the global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks registry. Replace (default) overwrites the registry with the user-supplied list — matches the legacy init.sqf pattern of assigning ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] directly. Append keeps the existing entries and adds the user-supplied list on top, deduped — useful when extending the stock list with mod-defined task types without losing the defaults. WARNING: legacy assignments to ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks in init.sqf / staticData.sqf execute AFTER module init and silently overwrite this setting. Use either the Eden picker or legacy init-time assignment, not both.</English>
    <Chinese>下方自訂任務清單如何合併進全域 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 註冊表。取代（預設）以使用者提供的清單覆蓋註冊表 — 與舊式於 init.sqf 直接指派 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] 的模式相符。附加保留既有項目,並在其上加入使用者提供的清單並去重 — 適合在擴充原始清單時加入模組定義的任務類型,而不失去預設值。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>下方自定义任务清单如何合并进全局 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 注册表。取代（默认）以用户提供的清单覆盖注册表 — 与旧式于 init.sqf 直接指派 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] 的模式相符。附加保留既有项目,并在其上加入用户提供的清单并去重 — 适合在扩充原始清单时加入模组定义的任务类型,而不失去默认值。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Cómo se combina la lista de tareas personalizadas con el registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (predeterminado) sobrescribe el registro con la lista proporcionada — equivale al patrón heredado de asignar ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] en init.sqf. Append conserva las entradas existentes y añade encima la lista proporcionada, deduplicada — útil para ampliar la lista estándar con tipos de tarea de mods sin perder los valores predeterminados.</Spanish>
    <French>Comment la liste de tâches personnalisées ci-dessous fusionne avec le registre global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (par défaut) écrase le registre avec la liste fournie — équivalent au modèle hérité d'assignation directe ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] dans init.sqf. Append conserve les entrées existantes et ajoute la liste fournie par-dessus, dédupliquée — utile pour étendre la liste standard avec des types de tâches de mods sans perdre les valeurs par défaut.</French>
    <Portuguese>Como a lista de tarefas personalizadas abaixo se mescla com o registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (padrão) sobrescreve o registro com a lista fornecida — equivale ao padrão herdado de atribuir ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] diretamente em init.sqf. Append mantém as entradas existentes e adiciona a lista fornecida em cima, deduplicada — útil para estender a lista padrão com tipos de tarefa de mods sem perder os valores padrão.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Как список пользовательских задач ниже объединяется с глобальным реестром ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks. Replace (по умолчанию) перезаписывает реестр переданным списком — соответствует прежнему шаблону присваивания ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks = [...] в init.sqf. Append сохраняет существующие записи и добавляет переданный список сверху с дедупликацией — полезно для расширения стандартного списка модовыми типами задач без потери значений по умолчанию.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_AUTOGEN_TASKS">
    <English>Override Auto-Generated Tasks:</English>
    <Chinese>覆寫自動生成任務：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>覆写自动生成任务：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Override tareas autogeneradas:</Spanish>
    <French>Override tâches auto-générées:</French>
    <Portuguese>Override tarefas autogeradas:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Перекрыть автогенерируемые задачи:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2_CUSTOM_AUTOGEN_TASKS_COMMENT">
    <English>Override the global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks registry — the pool of task types the AI commander draws from when auto-generating tasks for players. Tick task types from the listbox to keep them in the override set; type extra mod task types into the Override field with comma-separated names. Replace mode wipes the registry with your selection (the commander only generates the picked tasks); Append mode adds your selection on top of the stock list. Multi-select: left-click selects one row; Ctrl+left-click toggles individual rows; Shift+left-click selects a range.</English>
    <Chinese>覆寫全域 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 註冊表 — AI 指揮官為玩家自動生成任務時所從中抽取的任務類型池。在列表框中勾選要保留於覆寫集中的任務類型;在「覆寫」欄位以逗號分隔輸入額外的模組任務類型。取代模式會以您的選擇清除註冊表(指揮官僅生成所選任務);附加模式則在原始清單之上加入您的選擇。多選:左鍵點擊選取單一項目;Ctrl+左鍵點擊切換個別項目;Shift+左鍵點擊選取範圍。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>覆写全局 ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks 注册表 — AI 指挥官为玩家自动生成任务时所从中抽取的任务类型池。在列表框中勾选要保留于覆写集中的任务类型;在「覆写」字段以逗号分隔输入额外的模组任务类型。取代模式会以您的选择清除注册表(指挥官仅生成所选任务);附加模式则在原始清单之上加入您的选择。多选:左键点击选取单一项目;Ctrl+左键点击切换个别项目;Shift+左键点击选取范围。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Sobrescribe el registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — el pool de tipos de tarea del que el comandante IA extrae al autogenerar tareas para los jugadores. Marca tipos de tarea en el listbox para mantenerlos en el conjunto override; introduce tipos de tarea de mods adicionales en el campo Override con nombres separados por comas. El modo Replace borra el registro con tu selección (el comandante solo genera las tareas seleccionadas); el modo Append añade tu selección encima de la lista estándar. Selección múltiple: clic izquierdo selecciona una fila; Ctrl+clic izquierdo alterna filas individuales; Shift+clic izquierdo selecciona un rango.</Spanish>
    <French>Surcharge le registre global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — le vivier de types de tâches dans lequel le commandant IA puise pour auto-générer des tâches pour les joueurs. Cochez des types de tâches dans la liste pour les conserver dans l'ensemble override; saisissez des types de tâches de mods supplémentaires dans le champ Override avec des noms séparés par des virgules. Le mode Replace efface le registre avec votre sélection (le commandant ne génère que les tâches choisies); le mode Append ajoute votre sélection par-dessus la liste standard. Sélection multiple : clic gauche sélectionne une ligne ; Ctrl+clic gauche active/désactive des lignes individuelles ; Shift+clic gauche sélectionne une plage.</French>
    <Portuguese>Substitui o registro global ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — o pool de tipos de tarefa do qual o comandante IA extrai ao auto-gerar tarefas para os jogadores. Marque tipos de tarefa no listbox para mantê-los no conjunto override; insira tipos de tarefa de mods adicionais no campo Override com nomes separados por vírgulas. O modo Replace apaga o registro com a sua seleção (o comandante só gera as tarefas escolhidas); o modo Append adiciona a sua seleção sobre a lista padrão. Seleção múltipla: clique esquerdo seleciona uma linha; Ctrl+clique esquerdo alterna linhas individuais; Shift+clique esquerdo seleciona um intervalo.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Перекрывает глобальный реестр ALIVE_autoGeneratedTasks — пул типов задач, из которого ИИ-командир черпает при автогенерации задач для игроков. Отмечайте типы задач в списке, чтобы сохранить их в наборе override; вводите дополнительные модовые типы задач в поле Override через запятую. Режим Replace стирает реестр и заменяет его вашим выбором (командир генерирует только выбранные задачи); режим Append добавляет ваш выбор поверх стокового списка. Множественный выбор: левый клик выбирает одну строку; Ctrl+левый клик переключает отдельные строки; Shift+левый клик выбирает диапазон.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_MIN_DISTANCE">
    <English>Minimum Task Distance (m):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_MIN_DISTANCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Mission-wide minimum travel distance from the player when picking auto-generated Short / Medium / Long task locations. Set to 0 to disable.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_VIP_PANIC_TIMEOUT">
    <English>VIP Panic Timeout (s):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_VIP_PANIC_TIMEOUT_COMMENT">
    <English>How long, in seconds, a panicked VIP may remain uncontrolled before the VIP Escort task is marked failed.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_AO_RADIUS">
    <English>Task AO Radius (m):</English>
    <Chinese>任務 AO 半徑(米):</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>任务 AO 半径(米):</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Radio del AO de la tarea (m):</Spanish>
    <French>Rayon de l'AO de la tâche (m) :</French>
    <Portuguese>Raio do AO da tarefa (m):</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Радиус AO задачи (м):</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_TASK_AO_RADIUS_COMMENT">
    <English>Radius in metres of an optional ellipse marker drawn around each task position to highlight the search area. 0 disables (no circle drawn). Helps players locate task objectives in cluttered terrain where the standard task icon alone is hard to spot. Applies to all auto- and player-generated task markers.</English>
    <Chinese>圍繞每個任務位置繪製的可選橢圓標記的半徑(米),用以突顯搜索區域。0 表示停用(不繪製圓圈)。協助玩家在雜亂地形中定位任務目標,當標準任務圖示單獨難以辨識時尤為有用。適用於所有自動生成與玩家生成的任務標記。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>围绕每个任务位置绘制的可选椭圆标记的半径(米),用以突显搜索区域。0 表示停用(不绘制圆圈)。协助玩家在杂乱地形中定位任务目标,当标准任务图标单独难以辨识时尤为有用。适用于所有自动生成与玩家生成的任务标记。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Radio en metros de un marcador elíptico opcional dibujado alrededor de cada posición de tarea para destacar el área de búsqueda. 0 desactiva (no se dibuja círculo). Ayuda a los jugadores a localizar los objetivos de tarea en terreno saturado donde el icono de tarea estándar por sí solo resulta difícil de detectar. Se aplica a todos los marcadores de tarea autogenerados y generados por el jugador.</Spanish>
    <French>Rayon en mètres d'un marqueur ellipse optionnel tracé autour de chaque position de tâche pour mettre en évidence la zone de recherche. 0 désactive (aucun cercle tracé). Aide les joueurs à localiser les objectifs de tâche dans un terrain encombré où l'icône de tâche standard seule est difficile à repérer. S'applique à tous les marqueurs de tâche auto-générés et générés par le joueur.</French>
    <Portuguese>Raio em metros de um marcador elíptico opcional desenhado ao redor de cada posição de tarefa para destacar a área de busca. 0 desativa (nenhum círculo desenhado). Ajuda os jogadores a localizar os objetivos da tarefa em terreno carregado onde o ícone de tarefa padrão sozinho é difícil de identificar. Aplica-se a todos os marcadores de tarefa auto-gerados e gerados pelo jogador.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Радиус в метрах опционального эллиптического маркера, отрисовываемого вокруг каждой позиции задачи, чтобы выделить зону поиска. 0 отключает (круг не рисуется). Помогает игрокам находить цели задач на загромождённой местности, где стандартный значок задачи сам по себе трудно заметить. Применяется ко всем авто- и игроком сгенерированным маркерам задач.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_ENABLED">
    <English>Enable Civic-State COIN Model:</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_ENABLED_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables the multi-axis trust / security / services settlement model behind Hearts and Minds tasking. When ON: full 10-task family available (adds Medical Outreach, Checkpoint Partnership, Informant Exfiltration, Market Reopening on top of the legacy 6); per-cluster support state tracked across success / failure / retaliation events; cluster picker prefers settlements with rising insurgent pressure. When OFF: only the 6 legacy families spawn (Aid Delivery, Supply Convoy, Meet Local Leader, VIP Escort, Secure Community Event, Repair Critical Service); simpler success / failure scoring; cluster picker sorts purely by distance. Toggle this BEFORE picking entries in the multi-selects below - the listboxes filter their visible options based on this setting (re-open the attribute panel after toggling to refresh).</English>
    <Chinese>啟用支撐 Hearts and Minds 任務系統的多軸信任 / 安全 / 服務聚落模型。當開啟時:可使用完整的 10 任務家族(在原本 6 種之上新增 Medical Outreach、Checkpoint Partnership、Informant Exfiltration、Market Reopening);每個 cluster 的支援狀態在成功 / 失敗 / 報復事件之間追蹤;cluster 選取器偏好叛亂壓力上升的聚落。當關閉時:僅生成 6 個傳統家族(Aid Delivery、Supply Convoy、Meet Local Leader、VIP Escort、Secure Community Event、Repair Critical Service);更簡單的成功 / 失敗評分;cluster 選取器純粹按距離排序。在下方的多選清單中挑選項目之前先切換此項 - 列表框會根據此設定過濾其可見選項(切換後重新開啟屬性面板以刷新)。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>启用支撑 Hearts and Minds 任务系统的多轴信任 / 安全 / 服务聚落模型。当开启时:可使用完整的 10 任务家族(在原本 6 种之上新增 Medical Outreach、Checkpoint Partnership、Informant Exfiltration、Market Reopening);每个 cluster 的支援状态在成功 / 失败 / 报复事件之间追踪;cluster 选取器偏好叛乱压力上升的聚落。当关闭时:仅生成 6 个传统家族(Aid Delivery、Supply Convoy、Meet Local Leader、VIP Escort、Secure Community Event、Repair Critical Service);更简单的成功 / 失败评分;cluster 选取器纯粹按距离排序。在下方的多选清单中挑选项目之前先切换此项 - 列表框会根据此设定过滤其可见选项(切换后重新开启属性面板以刷新)。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Habilita el modelo de asentamiento multi-eje de confianza / seguridad / servicios que sustenta el tasking de Hearts and Minds. Cuando está ON: familia completa de 10 tareas disponible (añade Medical Outreach, Checkpoint Partnership, Informant Exfiltration, Market Reopening sobre las 6 legacy); estado de soporte por cluster rastreado a través de eventos de éxito / fracaso / represalia; el selector de cluster prefiere asentamientos con presión insurgente en aumento. Cuando está OFF: solo se generan las 6 familias legacy (Aid Delivery, Supply Convoy, Meet Local Leader, VIP Escort, Secure Community Event, Repair Critical Service); puntuación de éxito / fracaso más simple; el selector de cluster ordena puramente por distancia. Alterna esto ANTES de elegir entradas en los multi-selects de abajo - los listboxes filtran sus opciones visibles según este ajuste (vuelve a abrir el panel de atributos tras alternar para refrescar).</Spanish>
    <French>Active le modèle d'agglomération multi-axes confiance / sécurité / services derrière le tasking Hearts and Minds. Quand ON : famille complète de 10 tâches disponible (ajoute Medical Outreach, Checkpoint Partnership, Informant Exfiltration, Market Reopening en plus des 6 legacy) ; état de soutien par cluster suivi à travers les événements de succès / échec / représailles ; le sélecteur de cluster privilégie les agglomérations avec une pression insurgée croissante. Quand OFF : seules les 6 familles legacy sont générées (Aid Delivery, Supply Convoy, Meet Local Leader, VIP Escort, Secure Community Event, Repair Critical Service) ; scoring de succès / échec plus simple ; le sélecteur de cluster trie purement par distance. Basculez ceci AVANT de choisir des entrées dans les multi-sélections ci-dessous - les listboxes filtrent leurs options visibles selon ce réglage (rouvrez le panneau d'attributs après bascule pour rafraîchir).</French>
    <Portuguese>Habilita o modelo de assentamento multi-eixos de confiança / segurança / serviços por trás do tasking de Hearts and Minds. Quando ON: família completa de 10 tarefas disponível (adiciona Medical Outreach, Checkpoint Partnership, Informant Exfiltration, Market Reopening além das 6 legacy); estado de suporte por cluster rastreado através de eventos de sucesso / falha / retaliação; o seletor de cluster prefere assentamentos com pressão insurgente em alta. Quando OFF: somente as 6 famílias legacy são geradas (Aid Delivery, Supply Convoy, Meet Local Leader, VIP Escort, Secure Community Event, Repair Critical Service); pontuação de sucesso / falha mais simples; o seletor de cluster ordena puramente por distância. Alterne isto ANTES de escolher entradas nos multi-selects abaixo - os listboxes filtram suas opções visíveis com base nesta configuração (reabra o painel de atributos após alternar para atualizar).</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Включает многоосевую модель доверия / безопасности / услуг поселений, лежащую в основе системы задач Hearts and Minds. Когда ON: доступно полное семейство из 10 задач (добавляются Medical Outreach, Checkpoint Partnership, Informant Exfiltration, Market Reopening поверх 6 legacy); состояние поддержки по каждому cluster отслеживается через события успеха / провала / возмездия; селектор cluster предпочитает поселения с растущим повстанческим давлением. Когда OFF: генерируются только 6 legacy-семейств (Aid Delivery, Supply Convoy, Meet Local Leader, VIP Escort, Secure Community Event, Repair Critical Service); упрощённая оценка успеха / провала; селектор cluster сортирует исключительно по расстоянию. Переключайте это ДО выбора пунктов в мульти-селектах ниже - списки фильтруют свои видимые опции на основе этой настройки (после переключения откройте панель атрибутов заново для обновления).</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_SUCCESS">
    <English>Trust Success Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_SUCCESS_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to trust gains from successful Hearts and Minds tasks. 1.0 = stock; 2.0 = double; 0.5 = half. Affects how quickly local trust ramps in response to player effort.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_FAILURE">
    <English>Trust Failure Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_TRUST_FAILURE_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to trust losses from failed Hearts and Minds tasks or insurgent backlash events. Higher values make trust loss more punishing.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_SUCCESS">
    <English>Security Success Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_SUCCESS_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to security gains from successful Hearts and Minds tasks. Security feeds OPCOM hostility decay and insurgent-spawn suppression in settled areas.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_FAILURE">
    <English>Security Failure Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SECURITY_FAILURE_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to security losses from failed Hearts and Minds tasks or insurgent backlash events.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_SUCCESS">
    <English>Services Success Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_SUCCESS_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to services gains from successful Hearts and Minds tasks. Services represent functioning infrastructure and feed civilian-population cooperation events.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_FAILURE">
    <English>Services Failure Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_SERVICES_FAILURE_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to services losses from failed Hearts and Minds tasks or backlash events.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_COOLDOWN">
    <English>Civic Cooldown Multiplier:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_COOLDOWN_COMMENT">
    <English>Multiplier applied to Hearts and Minds task cooldown timers for the civic-state model. Higher values make a settlement wait longer between civic task offers.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DUP_PENALTY">
    <English>Duplicate Task Penalty (0-1):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DUP_PENALTY_COMMENT">
    <English>Penalty strength applied when the same Hearts and Minds task type repeats in the same settlement. Range 0-1; default 0.15 = 15% reward reduction per recent repeat.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_FAMILIES">
    <English>Enabled Civic Task Families:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_FAMILIES_COMMENT">
    <English>Pick one or more Hearts-and-Minds task families that civic-state generation may produce. Untick a family to exclude it from the generation pool. The Override field accepts free-text mod-defined task ids the listbox doesn't surface.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_WEIGHTS">
    <English>Civic Task Weights:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_WEIGHTS_COMMENT">
    <English>Comma-separated TaskType=Weight pairs used by civic-state task selection (no spaces). Higher weights make a task type more likely to be picked. Long string — edit in an external editor and paste.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DEBUG_INTEL">
    <English>Show Civic Debug Intel:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_CIVIC_DEBUG_INTEL_COMMENT">
    <English>Appends civic-state trust / security / services summaries to the description text of generated Hearts and Minds tasks. Useful for mission-maker tuning; turn off for player-facing missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_FACTIONS">
    <English>Auto Task Factions:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_C2ISTAR_AUTOGEN_FACTIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>Picks one faction per slot for the six per-side auto-task lanes (BLU Friendly / BLU Enemy / OPF Friendly / OPF Enemy / IND Friendly / IND Enemy). Click Next &gt; on the top filter row to cycle through the slots; the listbox shows the faction currently assigned to that slot. The bottom filter row cycles between Auto (narrows the listbox to the slot's natural side) and All (every military faction visible).</English>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
