<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<Project name="missions_coalive">
<Package name="Actions">
</Package>
<Package name="Descriptions">
<Key ID="STR_VN_MISSIONS_DESC_MISSION_ALIVE_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>PAVN and VC Forces continue to hold key areas with in the Khe Sanh valley. With limited resources at your disposal, defend Khe Sanh and conduct counter insurgency operations from FSB Old French Fort.</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_MISSIONS_MINDESC_MISSION_ALIVE_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>PAVN and VC Forces continue to hold key areas with in the Khe Sanh valley.</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
</Package>
<Package name="General">
<Key ID="STR_VN_MISSIONS_AUTH_MISSION_ALIVE_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>ALiVE Mod Team || Mission by Jman</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
</Package>
<Package name="Misc">
</Package>
<Package name="Debrief">
</Package>
<Package name="CO01 Briefing">
<Key ID="STR_VN_BRIEFING_COALIVE_ALIVEHOWTO_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>ALiVE populates the entire map with a full scale war. The AI commanders determine the strategy and use conventional or asymmetric warfare tactics to achieve their goals. Infantry, motorized, mechanized, armored units and aircraft are used to capture or defend strategic objectives across the area of operations.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;AI commanders will call in resupply and reinforcements, close air support and air strikes and recruit insurgencts from the civilian population to plant IEDs and conduct sabotage. Meanwhile, the civilian population actively support or turn against combatants based on their actions and interactions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As a squad playing an ALiVE mission, you must work together to use the tools at your disposal to patrol, identify and attack enemy units, positions and assets. Player Commanders using the ALiVE Menu can manage operations and tasks in coordination with AI commanders.</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_BRIEFING_COALIVE_ALIVEMENUINTER_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>The ALiVE Menu can be activated using the RIGHT APP MENU key (or a user defined key 20).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For ADMINS, the ALiVE Menu offers the chance to debug issues, teleport players, access the debug console and more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For PLAYERS, the ALiVE Menu offers some basic settings and a chance to save your position and loadout.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Using the scroll wheel,PLAYERS can interact with civilians to question them on the local situation and influence them by giving them rations. Civilians won't forgive collateral damage.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Using the map, PLAYERS can leave SPOTREPS and ADVANCED MARKERS by hitting the LEFT CTRL key when creating a map marker.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For PLAYER COMMANDERS with an appropriate radio (PRC-77) the ALiVE Menu enables you to access COMMANDER ACTIONS to manage personnel, logistics, tasks, combat support and more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_BRIEFING_COALIVE_ALIVEACTIONS_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>ALiVE COMMANDER ACTIONS (requires PRC-77)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Press the ALiVE Menu key to access Commander Actions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Personnel - Move players and AI units between groups&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Intel - Provides access to your side's AI Commander objectives as well as marking any known units on the map.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Logistics - Call in resupplies, from individuals and groups to vehicles, weapons and fortifications. Use convoys, airdrop or airlift.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tasks - Request tasks from the AI commander in order to contribute to the overall battlefield situation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Operations - Direct AI groups and issue waypoints or join AI controlled groups and fight alongside them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Combat Support - Request artillery, close air support or transport from assets within the AO.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Reports - Commanders can leave PATROLREPS and SITREPS in order to keep other commanders up to date with player and enemy activities.</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_BRIEFING_COALIVE_SITUATION_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>&lt;img image=&quot;pics\splash.paa&quot; width=&quot;380&quot; height=&quot;190&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;PAVN forces are conducting a major offensive from the North.  Int indicates approx Battalion strength enemy forces in the Area of Operations with good lines of communications enabling regular resupply and battle casualty replacements.  Meanwhile VC are conducting an insurgency operation in the West as a diversion which could grow into a significant threat if left unchecked.</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish>.</Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_BRIEFING_COALIVE_MISSION_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>&lt;img image=&quot;pics\mission.paa&quot; width=&quot;380&quot; height=&quot;190&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your squad is initially tasked with defending &lt;marker name='FOB2'&gt;FOB Khe Sanh&lt;/marker&gt; and subsequently conducting counter insurgency ops based out of &lt;marker name='FSB'&gt;FSB French Fort</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_BRIEFING_COALIVE_TACTICAL_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>&lt;img image=&quot;pics\tactical.paa&quot; width=&quot;380&quot; height=&quot;190&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;marker name='CS'&gt;Combat Support&lt;/marker&gt; and &lt;marker name='CSS'&gt;Combat Service Support&lt;/marker&gt; assets are available including Support Helicopters, Artillery, Mortars and a Cobra Attack Helicopter on call for Close Air Support.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are a limited number of PRC-77 radios available for the RTO to request and coord support from HQ.  Don't lose them!&lt;br/&gt;The Duty Officer at each FOB location can despatch you directly to your squad (is enabled in mission settings).</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_BRIEFING_COALIVE_EXECUTION_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>&lt;img image=&quot;pics\execution.paa&quot; width=&quot;380&quot; height=&quot;190&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Establish a defensive perimeter at the FOB and neutralise enemy forces advancing from the North.  You have the option to redeploy to the FSB and conduct fighting patrols throughout the Western AO to find and neutralise insurgent forces.  Alternatively, you can continue to fight the PAVN forces in the North</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
</Package>
<Package name="Parameters">
<Key ID="STR_VN_COALIVE_PARAMS_MAPMARKERS_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>Side Map Markers</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_PARAMS_ROTORLIB_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>Enable Advanced Rotor Flight Model</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
</Package>
<Package name="Titles">
<Key ID="STR_VN_MISSIONS_TITLE_MISSION_ALIVE_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>ALiVE | Khe Sanh Valley</English>
<French></French>
<German></German>
<Italian></Italian>
<Portuguese></Portuguese>
<Russian></Russian>
<Spanish></Spanish>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_VN_MISSIONS_AUTHOR_ALIVE_KHESANHVALLEY">
<Chinese></Chinese>
<English>ALiVE Mod Team</English>
<French>ALiVE Mod Team</French>
<German>ALiVE Mod Team</German>
<Italian>ALiVE Mod Team</Italian>
<Portuguese>ALiVE Mod Team</Portuguese>
<Russian>ALiVE Mod Team</Russian>
<Spanish>ALiVE Mod Team</Spanish>
</Key>
</Package>
<Package name="Waypoints">
</Package>
</Project>
