<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR">
    <English>Player Combat Logistics</English>
    <Chinesesimp>玩家战斗后勤</Chinesesimp>
    <Chinese>玩家戰鬥後勤</Chinese>
    <Spanish>Logística de combate del jugador</Spanish>
    <French>Logistique de combat joueur</French>
    <Portuguese>Logística de combate do jogador</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Боевое снабжение игрока</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_COMMENT">
    <English>Resupply players with logistics requests</English>
    <Chinesesimp>为玩家提供后勤补给</Chinesesimp>
    <Chinese>透過後勤請求為玩家補給</Chinese>
    <Spanish>Reabastece a los jugadores mediante solicitudes logísticas</Spanish>
    <French>Réapprovisionne les joueurs via des demandes logistiques</French>
    <Portuguese>Reabastece jogadores através de solicitações logísticas</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Пополняет припасы игроков через логистические запросы</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Writes Player Combat Logistics diagnostic logging to the RPT (resupply requests, deliveries and catalog resolution).</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_ALLOW">
    <English>Trigger Item Categories:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_ALLOW_COMMENT">
    <English>Pick one or more equipment categories. The player can access the resupply tablet if they carry any item from any ticked category (e.g. Laser Designators covers vanilla and mod-supplied designator classes). Categories from unloaded mods drop off the list automatically. Defaults to Laser Designators. For mod-supplied items that don't belong to a registered category, use the Custom Trigger Items (classnames) field below to add their classnames directly.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_CUSTOM_ITEMS">
    <English>Custom Trigger Items (classnames):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_CUSTOM_ITEMS_COMMENT">
    <English>Comma-separated list of additional item classnames that should grant resupply tablet access on top of the Trigger Item Categories above. Use this for mod-supplied items that don't fit a registered category (e.g. a custom faction's command tablet, a campaign-specific radio). Classnames are matched literally and case-insensitively against the player's assigned items / uniform / vest / backpack. Example: "MyMod_CommandTablet, AnotherMod_FieldRadio". Leave empty for none.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_AUDIO">
    <English>Radio Messages (Audio):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_AUDIO_COMMENT">
    <English>Uses audible radio messages for resupply requests and deliveries.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_TYPE">
    <English>Restriction Type:</English>
    <Chinese>限制類型：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>限制类型：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Tipo de restricción:</Spanish>
    <French>Type de restriction:</French>
    <Portuguese>Tipo de restrição:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Тип ограничения:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_TYPE_COMMENT">
    <English>Controls which vehicles and groups are available to the player.\n\n• Side — shows the player's side-wide assets, narrowed to the active friendly factions (see Filter Friendly Factions below).\n• Faction — shows only assets from the player's own faction, or from the factions ticked in the Factions list below.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_TYPE_SIDE">
    <English>Side</English>
    <Chinesesimp>阵营</Chinesesimp>
    <Chinese>陣營</Chinese>
    <Spanish>Bando</Spanish>
    <French>Camp</French>
    <Portuguese>Lado</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Сторона</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_TYPE_FACTION">
    <English>Faction</English>
    <Chinesesimp>派系</Chinesesimp>
    <Chinese>派系</Chinese>
    <Spanish>Facción</Spanish>
    <French>Faction</French>
    <Portuguese>Facção</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Фракция</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_FACTION_WHITELIST">
    <English>Factions:</English>
    <Chinese>派系：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>派系：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Facciones:</Spanish>
    <French>Factions:</French>
    <Portuguese>Facções:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Фракции:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_FACTION_WHITELIST_COMMENT">
    <English>Select the factions whose vehicles and groups are available for resupply. If left empty, defaults to the player's faction at runtime. Use the manual field below for factions not shown in the list. Multi-select: left-click selects one row; Ctrl+left-click toggles individual rows; Shift+left-click selects a range.</English>
    <Chinese>選取載具與小組可用於補給的派系。若留空,執行時預設為玩家所屬派系。下方手動欄位可用於清單未顯示的派系。多選:左鍵點擊選取單一項目;Ctrl+左鍵點擊切換個別項目;Shift+左鍵點擊選取範圍。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>选取载具与小组可用于补给的派系。若留空,执行时默认为玩家所属派系。下方手动字段可用于清单未显示的派系。多选:左键点击选取单一项目;Ctrl+左键点击切换个别项目;Shift+左键点击选取范围。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Selecciona las facciones cuyos vehículos y grupos están disponibles para el reabastecimiento. Si se deja vacío, recurre a la facción del jugador en tiempo de ejecución. Usa el campo manual de abajo para facciones que no aparezcan en la lista. Selección múltiple: clic izquierdo selecciona una fila; Ctrl+clic izquierdo alterna filas individuales; Shift+clic izquierdo selecciona un rango.</Spanish>
    <French>Sélectionnez les factions dont les véhicules et les groupes sont disponibles pour le réapprovisionnement. Si laissé vide, utilise la faction du joueur à l'exécution. Utilisez le champ manuel ci-dessous pour les factions qui n'apparaissent pas dans la liste. Sélection multiple : clic gauche sélectionne une ligne ; Ctrl+clic gauche active/désactive des lignes individuelles ; Shift+clic gauche sélectionne une plage.</French>
    <Portuguese>Selecione as facções cujos veículos e grupos estão disponíveis para reabastecimento. Se deixado vazio, recorre à facção do jogador em tempo de execução. Use o campo manual abaixo para facções não exibidas na lista. Seleção múltipla: clique esquerdo seleciona uma linha; Ctrl+clique esquerdo alterna linhas individuais; Shift+clique esquerdo seleciona um intervalo.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Выберите фракции, чьи техника и группы доступны для пополнения. Если оставить пустым, по умолчанию используется фракция игрока в рантайме. Используйте поле ручного ввода ниже для фракций, не показанных в списке. Множественный выбор: левый клик выбирает одну строку; Ctrl+левый клик переключает отдельные строки; Shift+левый клик выбирает диапазон.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_FACTION_WHITELIST_MANUAL">
    <English>Factions (manual override):</English>
    <Chinese>派系（手動覆蓋）：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>派系（手动覆盖）：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Facciones (anulación manual):</Spanish>
    <French>Factions (remplacement manuel)&#xa0;:</French>
    <Portuguese>Facções (substituição manual):</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Фракции (ручное переопределение):</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_FACTION_WHITELIST_MANUAL_COMMENT">
    <English>Optional. Type extra faction classnames for mods not currently loaded but expected at mission time. Format: comma-separated classnames with no spaces or quotes — e.g. OPF_F,rhs_faction_msv. Combined with the Factions multi-select above at runtime.</English>
    <Chinese>可選。輸入目前未載入的模組派系類名，格式：逗號分隔，無空格，無引號。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>可选。输入当前未加载的模组派系类名，格式：逗号分隔，无空格，无引号。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Opcional. Escriba classnames de facciones adicionales para mods no cargados actualmente. Formato: nombres separados por comas, sin espacios ni comillas.</Spanish>
    <French>Facultatif. Saisissez les classnames de factions supplémentaires pour les mods non chargés actuellement. Format : noms séparés par des virgules, sans espaces ni guillemets.</French>
    <Portuguese>Opcional. Digite classnames de facções adicionais para mods não carregados atualmente. Formato: nomes separados por vírgulas, sem espaços ou aspas.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Необязательно. Введите classnames дополнительных фракций для незагруженных модов. Формат: имена через запятую, без пробелов и кавычек.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_FILTER_FRIENDLY_FACTIONS">
    <English>Filter Friendly Factions:</English>
    <Chinese>篩選友軍派系：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>筛选友军派系：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Filtrar facciones aliadas:</Spanish>
    <French>Filtrer les factions alliées:</French>
    <Portuguese>Filtrar facções aliadas:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Фильтр дружественных фракций:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_FILTER_FRIENDLY_FACTIONS_COMMENT">
    <English>When enabled, both the Supply List (vehicles) and the Reinforce List (groups) only show factions actively commanded by OPCOM modules friendly to the player's side. Disable to show all config factions. Has no effect if the Factions list above is set.</English>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_DELIVERY_AIRDROP">
    <English>Allow Airdrop:</English>
    <Chinese>允許空投：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>允许空投：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Permitir lanzamiento aéreo:</Spanish>
    <French>Autoriser le largage aérien:</French>
    <Portuguese>Permitir lançamento aéreo:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Разрешить десантирование:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_DELIVERY_AIRDROP_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow players to request supplies via Air Drop</English>
    <Chinesesimp>允许玩家通过空投请求补给</Chinesesimp>
    <Chinese>允許玩家透過空投請求補給</Chinese>
    <Spanish>Permite a los jugadores solicitar suministros mediante lanzamiento aéreo</Spanish>
    <French>Permet aux joueurs de demander du ravitaillement par largage aérien</French>
    <Portuguese>Permite aos jogadores solicitar suprimentos via lançamento aéreo</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Разрешает игрокам запрашивать припасы через десантирование</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_DELIVERY_INSERT">
    <English>Allow Heli/VTOL:</English>
    <Chinese>允許直升機/VTOL：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>允许直升机/VTOL：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Permitir helicóptero/VTOL:</Spanish>
    <French>Autoriser hélicoptère/VTOL:</French>
    <Portuguese>Permitir helicóptero/VTOL:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Разрешить вертолёт/VTOL:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_DELIVERY_INSERT_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow players to request supplies via Helicopter/VTOL</English>
    <Chinesesimp>允许玩家通过直升机/垂直起降请求补给</Chinesesimp>
    <Chinese>允許玩家透過直升機/VTOL 請求補給</Chinese>
    <Spanish>Permite a los jugadores solicitar suministros mediante helicóptero/VTOL</Spanish>
    <French>Permet aux joueurs de demander du ravitaillement par hélicoptère/VTOL</French>
    <Portuguese>Permite aos jogadores solicitar suprimentos via helicóptero/VTOL</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Разрешает игрокам запрашивать припасы через вертолёт/VTOL</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_DELIVERY_CONVOY">
    <English>Allow Convoy:</English>
    <Chinese>允許車隊：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>允许车队：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Permitir convoy:</Spanish>
    <French>Autoriser convoi:</French>
    <Portuguese>Permitir comboio:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Разрешить конвой:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_DELIVERY_CONVOY_COMMENT">
    <English>Allow players to request supplies via Convoy</English>
    <Chinesesimp>允许玩家通过车队请求补给</Chinesesimp>
    <Chinese>允許玩家透過車隊請求補給</Chinese>
    <Spanish>Permite a los jugadores solicitar suministros mediante convoy</Spanish>
    <French>Permet aux joueurs de demander du ravitaillement par convoi</French>
    <Portuguese>Permite aos jogadores solicitar suprimentos via comboio</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Разрешает игрокам запрашивать припасы через конвой</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_BLACKLIST">
    <English>Item Blacklist:</English>
    <Chinese>物品黑名單：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>物品黑名单：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Lista negra de objetos:</Spanish>
    <French>Liste noire des objets:</French>
    <Portuguese>Lista negra de itens:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Чёрный список предметов:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_BLACKLIST_COMMENT">
    <English>Comma-separated list of config class names to exclude from the resupply catalog (e.g. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Class names are case-sensitive.</English>
    <Chinese>以逗號分隔的設定類別名稱清單,將從補給目錄中排除（例如 Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F）。類別名稱區分大小寫。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>以逗号分隔的配置类别名称清单,将从补给目录中排除（例如 Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F）。类别名称区分大小写。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Lista separada por comas de nombres de clase del config a excluir del catálogo de reabastecimiento (p. ej. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Los nombres de clase distinguen mayúsculas y minúsculas.</Spanish>
    <French>Liste séparée par des virgules de noms de classes du config à exclure du catalogue de réapprovisionnement (ex. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Les noms de classe sont sensibles à la casse.</French>
    <Portuguese>Lista separada por vírgulas de nomes de classes do config a excluir do catálogo de reabastecimento (ex. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Os nomes de classe são sensíveis a maiúsculas/minúsculas.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Список через запятую имён классов конфига, исключаемых из каталога снабжения (например, Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Имена классов чувствительны к регистру.</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_WHITELIST">
    <English>Item Whitelist:</English>
    <Chinese>物品白名單：</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>物品白名单：</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Lista blanca de objetos:</Spanish>
    <French>Liste blanche des objets:</French>
    <Portuguese>Lista de permissões de itens:</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Белый список предметов:</Russian>
</Key>
<!-- AI-translated; native-speaker review welcome -->
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_PR_RESTRICTION_WHITELIST_COMMENT">
    <English>Comma-separated list of config class names to restrict the resupply catalog to. Only these classes will appear (e.g. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Class names are case-sensitive.</English>
    <Chinese>以逗號分隔的設定類別名稱清單,用於將補給目錄限制為僅這些類別（例如 Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F）。類別名稱區分大小寫。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>以逗号分隔的配置类别名称清单,用于将补给目录限制为仅这些类别（例如 Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F）。类别名称区分大小写。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Lista separada por comas de nombres de clase del config para restringir el catálogo de reabastecimiento únicamente a estas clases (p. ej. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Solo aparecerán estas clases. Los nombres de clase distinguen mayúsculas y minúsculas.</Spanish>
    <French>Liste séparée par des virgules de noms de classes du config pour restreindre le catalogue de réapprovisionnement à ces seules classes (ex. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Seules ces classes apparaîtront. Les noms de classe sont sensibles à la casse.</French>
    <Portuguese>Lista separada por vírgulas de nomes de classes do config para restringir o catálogo de reabastecimento apenas a estas classes (ex. Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Apenas estas classes aparecerão. Os nomes de classe são sensíveis a maiúsculas/minúsculas.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Список через запятую имён классов конфига, ограничивающий каталог снабжения только этими классами (например, Box_IND_Ammo_F,B_MRAP_01_F). Появятся только эти классы. Имена классов чувствительны к регистру.</Russian>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
