<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL">
    <English>Military AI Skill</English>
	<Chinesesimp>军事人工智能技能</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_COMMENT">
    <English>Set AI Skill levels per faction by presets or custom settings</English>
	<Chinesesimp>通过预设或自定义设置设置每个派系的人工智能技能等级</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_ERROR1">
    <English>Only one AI SKILL module allowed</English>
	<Chinesesimp>只允许一个人工智能技能模块</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>启用调试：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Enables AI Skill Module Debug</English>
	<Chinesesimp>启用人工智能技能模组调试</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_RECRUIT">
    <English>Recruit Factions:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>招募派系：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_RECRUIT_COMMENT">
    <English>Units of these factions will use Recruit-tier skill values (low accuracy, slow reactions, short detection range). Lowest preset — use for untrained militia or irregular forces. Preset values are fixed. To assign exact per-parameter values to a faction, use the Custom Skill Values section below instead.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_REGULAR">
    <English>Regular Factions:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>常规派系：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_REGULAR_COMMENT">
    <English>Units of these factions will use Regular-tier skill values (moderate accuracy, average reactions). Baseline preset suitable for most conventional forces. Preset values are fixed. To assign exact per-parameter values to a faction, use the Custom Skill Values section below instead.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_VETERAN">
    <English>Veteran Factions:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>资深派系：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_VETERAN_COMMENT">
    <English>Units of these factions will use Veteran-tier skill values (good accuracy, faster reactions, better spotting). Use for experienced infantry or special operations forces. Preset values are fixed. To assign exact per-parameter values to a faction, use the Custom Skill Values section below instead.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_EXPERT">
    <English>Expert Factions:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>专家派系：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_EXPERT_COMMENT">
    <English>Units of these factions will use Expert-tier skill values (high accuracy, fast reactions, long detection range). Highest preset — use for top-tier special forces. Preset values are fixed. To assign exact per-parameter values to a faction, use the Custom Skill Values section below instead.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_FACTIONS_MANUAL">
    <English>Factions (manual override):</English>
    <Chinese>派系（手動覆蓋）:</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>派系（手动覆盖）:</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Facciones (anulación manual):</Spanish>
    <French>Factions (remplacement manuel)&#xa0;:</French>
    <Portuguese>Facções (substituição manual):</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Фракции (ручное переопределение):</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_FACTIONS_MANUAL_COMMENT">
    <English>Optional. Type extra faction classnames for mods not currently loaded but expected at mission time. Format: comma-separated classnames with no spaces or quotes — e.g. OPF_F,rhs_faction_msv. Combined with the Factions multi-select above at runtime.</English>
    <Chinese>可選。輸入目前未載入的模組派系類名，格式：逗號分隔，無空格，無引號。</Chinese>
    <Chinesesimp>可选。输入当前未加载的模组派系类名，格式：逗号分隔，无空格，无引号。</Chinesesimp>
    <Spanish>Opcional. Escriba classnames de facciones adicionales para mods no cargados actualmente. Formato: nombres separados por comas, sin espacios ni comillas.</Spanish>
    <French>Facultatif. Saisissez les classnames de factions supplémentaires pour les mods non chargés actuellement. Format : noms séparés par des virgules, sans espaces ni guillemets.</French>
    <Portuguese>Opcional. Digite classnames de facções adicionais para mods não carregados atualmente. Formato: nomes separados por vírgulas, sem espaços ou aspas.</Portuguese>
    <Russian>Необязательно. Введите classnames дополнительных фракций для незагруженных модов. Формат: имена через запятую, без пробелов и кавычек.</Russian>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM">
    <English>Factions:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_COMMENT">
    <English>Factions whose units will receive the exact skill values you configure below. This section is independent of the preset tiers above — presets use fixed hardcoded values, while this section gives full control over each parameter. If a faction is also assigned to a preset tier, the custom values take precedence. Leave empty to apply no custom values.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_ABILITY_MIN">
    <English>Minimum Ability:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>最低能力：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_ABILITY_MIN_COMMENT">
    <English>Minimum general ability (0.0–1.0). Combined with maximum to give each unit a random ability value within the range. Lower = weaker AI overall.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>最低能力</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_ABILITY_MAX">
    <English>Maximum Ability:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>最大能力：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_ABILITY_MAX_COMMENT">
    <English>Maximum general ability (0.0–1.0). Combined with minimum to give each unit a random ability value within the range. Higher = stronger AI overall.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>最大能力</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_AIM_ACCURACY">
    <English>Aim Accuracy:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>瞄准精度：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_AIM_ACCURACY_COMMENT">
    <English>How accurately the unit aims (0.0–1.0). Lower values cause more scatter. Works alongside Aim Shake and Aim Speed.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>瞄准精度</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_AIM_SHAKE">
    <English>Aim Shake:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>瞄准摇晃：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_AIM_SHAKE_COMMENT">
    <English>How much the unit's aim wobbles between shots (0.0–1.0). Higher values increase weapon sway. Works alongside Aim Accuracy.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>瞄准摇晃</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_AIM_SPEED">
    <English>Aim Speed:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_AIM_SPEED_COMMENT">
    <English>How quickly the unit acquires and tracks targets (0.0–1.0). Higher values mean faster target acquisition.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_ENDURANCE">
    <English>Endurance (unused):</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_ENDURANCE_COMMENT">
    <English>No effect in Arma 3 — the endurance sub-skill has been ignored by the engine since early development. Value is accepted but never applied. This field will be removed in a future version.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_SPOT_DISTANCE">
    <English>Spot Distance:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>发现距离：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_SPOT_DISTANCE_COMMENT">
    <English>Maximum detection range multiplier (0.0–1.0). Higher values allow the unit to spot enemies at greater distances.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>发现距离</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_SPOT_TIME">
    <English>Spot Time:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>发现时间：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_SPOT_TIME_COMMENT">
    <English>How quickly the unit spots a detected enemy (0.0–1.0). Lower values mean the unit is slower to confirm and react to contacts.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>发现时间</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_COURAGE">
    <English>Courage:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>勇气：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_COURAGE_COMMENT">
    <English>Unit willingness to advance and engage under fire (0.0–1.0). Lower values make units more likely to fall back or suppress rather than assault.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>勇气</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_FLEEING">
    <English>Cowardice:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>怯懦：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_FLEEING_COMMENT">
    <English>Likelihood that the unit abandons combat and retreats when under fire (0.0–1.0). Higher values make units more prone to fleeing. Lower values keep them engaged longer. Works alongside Courage.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_RELOAD">
    <English>Reload:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>装填：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_RELOAD_COMMENT">
    <English>How quickly the unit attempts to reload after firing (0.0–1.0). Higher values reduce reload time.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>装填</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_COMMANDING">
    <English>Commanding:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>指挥：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_COMMANDING_COMMENT">
    <English>Quality of the unit's command decisions when acting as a group leader (0.0–1.0). Higher values improve squad-level tactics and target prioritisation.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>指挥</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_GENERAL">
    <English>General:</English>
	<Chinesesimp>将军：</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_AISKILL_CUSTOM_GENERAL_COMMENT">
    <English>Overall AI skill multiplier (0.0–1.0). Acts as a global modifier affecting all other skill traits. Set lower to broadly weaken a faction without adjusting individual values.</English>
	<Chinesesimp>将军</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
