<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Project name="Arma3">
<Package name="ALiVE">
<Container name="STR_DN">
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO">
    <English>Military Air Component Commander</English>
    <Chinesesimp>军事空军部队指挥官</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_COMMENT">
    <English>Joint Forces Air Component Commander</English>
    <Chinesesimp>联合部队空中部队指挥官</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_DEBUG">
    <English>Enable Debug:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>启用调试</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_DEBUG_COMMENT">
    <English>Verbose logging to the RPT file, plus map markers at the HQ, field HQ and hangar positions this module picks. Those markers are global - every player sees them, not just admins - and are never removed, so leave this off for live missions.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PERSISTENT">
    <English>Persistent:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>持久的</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PERSISTENT_COMMENT">
    <English>Saves this module's aircraft roster - which aircraft exist and which airspace each belongs to - to the ALiVE database between sessions. Turning it on for any one MACC saves the roster for all of them. The HQ, runway overrides and any tasking in progress are never saved and are worked out fresh on every load.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_BROADCASTONRADIO">
    <English>Radio Messages:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>无线电信息</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_BROADCASTONRADIO_COMMENT">
    <English>HQ radio traffic, heard only by players on this module's own side: mission acknowledged or denied, aircraft lost, and base compromised. No silences all of it except the one-off 'forward airbase established' call at mission start, which always plays.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_DRONE_TYPES">
    <English>Drone Types:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_DRONE_TYPES_COMMENT">
    <English>Tick the drones this commander may place. Ctrl-click to select more than one. Leave everything unticked to use whatever drones the faction itself lists, which is the usual choice. Worth setting when a faction has none of its own, which is common even where the mod provides them. The list covers every drone the loaded content offers.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PLACE_DRONES">
    <English>Place Drones:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PLACE_DRONES_COMMENT">
    <English>Places one of the faction's drones at the base at mission start, on a helipad if there is one. Separate from Place Air Assets, so an air component can consist of drones alone. Unarmed reconnaissance drones count - they are the ones most worth having. Does nothing if Use Drones is set to No.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_USE_UAVS">
    <English>Use Drones:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_USE_UAVS_COMMENT">
    <English>Whether this commander may fly unmanned aircraft. They are adopted from the airspace like any other aircraft and need no aircrew, so a reconnaissance drone can be tasked while every pilot is busy. Set to No and drones in this airspace are left alone entirely, for anyone else to use.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_SORTIE_DURATION">
    <English>Sortie Duration:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_SORTIE_DURATION_COMMENT">
    <English>Minutes a sortie is allowed to run before the aircraft is recalled, in whole minutes. This also sets how long an aircraft waits for its pilot and how long it loiters on task. Leave blank to use whatever the requesting commander asks for, which is usually 10.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_MIN_ASSETS">
    <English>Minimum Aircraft For Offensive Missions:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_MIN_ASSETS_COMMENT">
    <English>Once this many aircraft or fewer remain, the commander stops flying offensive missions and keeps only Combat Air Patrol and Defensive Counter-Air until numbers recover. Leave blank for the default, which is 4 aircraft when the roster was restored from a save and 2 otherwise.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PILOTBUILDING">
    <English>Pilot Ready Room:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>飞行员准备室</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PILOTBUILDING_COMMENT">
    <English>Classname of a building within 50 m of this module where replacement aircrew appear, for example Land_Cargo_House_V3_F. Leave blank to pick a nearby building automatically. A classname that matches nothing within 50 m puts the crew out in the open at the module's own position, which is worse than leaving it blank.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RUNWAYSTARTPOS">
    <English>Runway start position:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>跑道起始位置:</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RUNWAYSTARTPOS_COMMENT">
    <English>Advanced override. One end of the runway centreline, format [x,y,z]. Stops other ALiVE systems placing compositions on the runway - it does not affect where aircraft take off or land. Leave blank: ALiVE detects real runways and taxiways on its own.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RUNWAYENDPOS">
    <English>Runway end position:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>跑道终点位置:</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RUNWAYENDPOS_COMMENT">
    <English>Advanced override. The other end of the runway centreline, format [x,y,z]. Pairs with Runway start position - see that tooltip. Only drawn on the map when Debug is on.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RUNWAYWIDTH">
    <English>Runway width:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>跑道宽度:</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RUNWAYWIDTH_COMMENT">
    <English>Advanced override. Width in metres of the no-placement zone around the centreline above. Leave blank if start and end position are blank. If those are set and this is not, a 24 m zone is used - the same as a vanilla runway.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_FACTION">
    <English>Faction:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>阵营</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_FACTION_COMMENT">
    <English>Seeds this module's aircraft list and permanently fixes its side, e.g. OPF_F. Factions from synced AI Commanders are added automatically, but only from Commanders whose side is friendly to this one; the rest are dropped without warning. An unrecognised classname does not error, it falls back to EAST. A synced Faction Compiler overrides this.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_TYPES">
    <English>Available ATOs:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>可用的ATO</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_TYPES_COMMENT">
    <English>Tick the air missions this commander may fly. Ctrl-click to select more than one. Suppression of Enemy Air Defences only detects anti-air sites - turn on Generate SEAD Tasks to have anything done about them. When few aircraft remain, the list is narrowed to Combat Air Patrol and Defensive Counter-Air on its own until numbers recover.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_AIRSPACE">
    <English>Airspace Markers:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>空域标记</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_AIRSPACE_COMMENT">
    <English>Marker names bounding this module's airspace, comma-separated, no spaces or quotes, e.g. marker1,marker2. Aircraft are never synced to this module: any armed aircraft of a managed faction already sitting inside one of these markers is adopted. Leave blank for the whole map. If none of the names match a real marker the module silently fails to start, so check the spelling.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_USAGE">
    <English>Place a MACC module to provide Combat Air Patrol and Defensive Counter-Air over your airspace. Sync it to an AI Commander module to enable Recce, Strike, Close Air Support and OCA requests. A Military AI Commander module must be present somewhere in the mission or MACC will not start.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_CREATE_HQ">
    <English>Build HQ If Needed:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_CREATE_HQ_COMMENT">
    <English>MACC always takes a military or headquarters building within 750 m of the module as its command post. This only decides what happens when there is none: Yes spawns a garrisoned field HQ composition, No falls back to a building at the nearest airbase with no garrison. A carrier-based MACC always uses the fallback. Either way air tasking stops while the enemy holds the ground around the HQ, and stops for good if it is destroyed.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PLACE_AIR">
    <English>Place Air Assets:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>放置飞行载具</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_PLACE_AIR_COMMENT">
    <English>If fewer than two armed aircraft start inside this module's airspace, extra ones are placed at the nearest airbase or helipad. Startup only - replacing later losses is what Resupply does. Has no effect on a carrier. Beware: with this off and no armed aircraft at all in the airspace, MACC never starts and nothing is tasked for the whole mission.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_GENERATE_TASKS">
    <English>Generate Player Tasks:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>生成玩家任务</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_GENERATE_TASKS_COMMENT">
    <English>Hands air missions to players as tasks, using the C2ISTAR module: search and rescue for downed aircrew, a backup interception call when several hostiles appear, and any mission with no free AI aircraft - that last only when a player is already flying the right type. AI tasking is unaffected either way; with No these are simply dropped, not held for later.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_GENERATE_SEADTASKS">
    <English>Generate SEAD Tasks:</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_GENERATE_SEADTASKS_COMMENT">
    <English>MACC does not send AI aircraft against detected anti-air sites. This only creates a player Air Tasking Order for them, and needs the C2ISTAR module. Leave this off and detected anti-air is recorded but never engaged.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RESUPPLY">
    <English>Resupply:</English>
    <Chinesesimp>重新补给</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RESUPPLY_COMMENT">
    <English>Replaces lost aircraft. If a Logistics Commander for the same faction is anywhere in the mission it flies the replacement in; otherwise MACC creates one itself at the original parking spot. Either way the new aircraft sits out a few minutes of maintenance before it can be tasked. With No, losses are permanent and the roster only ever shrinks.</English>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_NOT_ESTABLISHED">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, %2 forward airbase has not been established. No air assets available for tasking. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,这是%1,%2前方空军基地尚未建立。没有可用于任务的飞行载具。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_ESTABLISHED">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, %2 forward airbase established at grid %3, Air Tasking Orders to follow. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,这是%1,%2前方空军基地,在网格%3建立,空中任务命令如下。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_UNDER_ATTACK">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, %2 forward airbase at grid %3 is under attack by enemy forces, request immediate support. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,这里是%1,位于网格%3的%2前方空军基地正受到敌军的攻击,请求立即支援。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_OVERRUN">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, %2 forward airbase at grid %3 is compromised. Relocating to alternate. Air combat operations unavailable until further notice. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,这是%1,位于网格%3的%2前方空军基地已被攻破。重新定位到备用位置。空战行动在另行通知前不可用。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_REQUEST_ACKNOWLEDGED">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, %2 has requested %3 at grid %4. Air Tasking Order to follow. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号，这是%1, %2 已在网格 %4 请求 %3。执行空中任务命令。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_UNAVAILABLE">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, aircraft unavailable, air combat operations suspended. Requesting replen. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号，这里是 %1 ,飞机无法使用,空战行动暂停。请求重新规划。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_REQUEST_DENIED">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, request for %2 at grid %3 denied. Aircraft not available. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,这是%1,对网格%3上的%2的请求被拒绝。飞机不可用。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_START">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, scrambling %2 on ATO %3 at grid %4. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,这是 %1 ,正在对网格 %4 处的ATO %3 上的 %2 进行抢夺。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_AIRCRAFT_LOST">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, we've lost radar contact with a %2 on %3. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号，这里是%1,我们与 %3 上的 %2 失去雷达联系。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_ON_STATION">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, %2 on station at grid %3. Commencing %4 now. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,我是%1,%2,位于网格%3上的电台。现在开始%4。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RETURN">
    <English>on %1. Air tasking complete, I am RTB. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>%1。空中任务完成,这里是RTB。完毕</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RETURN_FUEL">
    <English>Bingo fuel, I am RTB. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>油量已达最低限度,这里RTB。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RETURN_AMMO">
    <English>Winchester, I am RTB. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>温彻斯特,这里是RTB,完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_RETURN_DAMAGE">
    <English>We've been hit, critical damage sustained, I am RTB. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>我们被击中了,受到严重伤害,我是RTB。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
<Key ID="STR_ALIVE_ATO_MISSION_COMPLETE">
    <English>All callsigns, this is %1, %2 is back at base, %3 mission complete. Out.</English>
    <Chinesesimp>所有呼号,这是 %1 , %2 已返回基地, %3 任务完成。完毕。</Chinesesimp>
</Key>
</Container></Package></Project>
